<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title>BEQCatalogue</title><description>A RSS feed containing all BEQs created in the last 2 weeks</description><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/</link><language>en-gb</language><pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 09:57:26 -0000</pubDate><atom:link href="https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/rss.xml" ref="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item><title>The Living Daylights</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/the-living-daylights/#dts-hd-ma-51-dd-51</link><description>After a defecting Russian general reveals a plot to assassinate foreign spies, James Bond is assigned a secret mission to dispatch the new head of the KGB to prevent an escalation of tensions between the Soviet Union and the West.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 09:54:32 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">75cc10d394cbcbd482698e85c0c9e34adc0445b129cd83c73badacca7b7d953a</guid></item><item><title>Moonraker</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/moonraker/#dts-hd-ma-51-dd-51</link><description>After Drax Industries' Moonraker space shuttle is hijacked, secret agent James Bond is assigned to investigate, traveling to California to meet the company's owner, the mysterious Hugo Drax. With the help of scientist Dr. Holly Goodhead, Bond soon uncovers Drax's nefarious plans for humanity, all the while fending off an old nemesis, Jaws, and venturing to Venice, Rio, the Amazon...and even outer space.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 09:54:32 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">631e21a4ff4afeb2851201aa9c32f6ec37786783fceb16520776476b21c78438</guid></item><item><title>The Man with the Golden Gun</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/the-man-with-the-golden-gun/#dts-hd-ma-51-dd-51</link><description>Cool government operative James Bond searches for a stolen invention that can turn the sun's heat into a destructive weapon. He soon crosses paths with the menacing Francisco Scaramanga, a hitman so skilled he has a seven-figure working fee. Bond then joins forces with the swimsuit-clad Mary Goodnight, and together they track Scaramanga to a Thai tropical isle hideout where the killer-for-hire lures the slick spy into a deadly maze for a final duel.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 09:54:32 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">99301d1b20c6ec5058ad40097ec017287387f6837ea28fa4001bbd62329ecdf9</guid></item><item><title>Octopussy</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/octopussy/#dts-hd-ma-51-dd-51</link><description>James Bond is sent to investigate after a fellow “00” agent is found dead with a priceless Indian Fabergé egg. Bond follows the mystery and uncovers a smuggling scandal and a Russian General who wants to provoke a new World War.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 09:54:32 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">cd2b8231cd0b65ce92b46f4e1d2d9f6fcb541cfd1d3d0ecdde02a2ddcc53188c</guid></item><item><title>Quantum of Solace</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/quantum-of-solace/#dd-51</link><description>Betrayed by Vesper, the woman he loved, 007 fights the urge to make his latest mission personal. Pursuing his determination to uncover the truth, Bond and M interrogate Mr. White, who reveals that the organization that blackmailed Vesper is far more complex and dangerous than anyone had imagined.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 09:54:32 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">f867d50e1b1e04ac878d99bd1001372c63ecd437df93e466390e80e2cf8993cf</guid></item><item><title>Skyfall</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/skyfall/#dts-hd-ma-51-dd-51</link><description>When Bond's latest assignment goes gravely wrong, agents around the world are exposed and MI6 headquarters is attacked. While M faces challenges to her authority and position from Gareth Mallory, the new Chairman of the Intelligence and Security Committee, it's up to Bond, aided only by field agent Eve, to locate the mastermind behind the attack.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 09:54:32 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">4ab815e8f24140dde052e26b4e4b8f75d349e1d1d591e3522d07485fb8a5ec7c</guid></item><item><title>Spectre</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/spectre/#dts-hd-ma-71-dd-51</link><description>A cryptic message from Bond’s past sends him on a trail to uncover a sinister organization. While M battles political forces to keep the secret service alive, Bond peels back the layers of deceit to reveal the terrible truth behind SPECTRE.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 09:54:32 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">6da90d715204c93381d2b4b25468f0ccec1feb323a4432c8f4a0fa7ed627f87e</guid></item><item><title>The Spy Who Loved Me</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/the-spy-who-loved-me/#dts-hd-ma-51-dd-51</link><description>Russian and British submarines with nuclear missiles on board both vanish from sight without a trace. England and Russia both blame each other as James Bond tries to solve the riddle of the disappearing ships. But the KGB also has an agent on the case.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 09:54:32 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">3ee7d0cbf75a88ad65c4a3d29f738a37a13d283b4b731950745538f2e03c5c58</guid></item><item><title>Thunderball</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/thunderball/#dd-51</link><description>A criminal organization has obtained two nuclear bombs and are asking for a 100 million pound ransom in the form of diamonds in seven days or they will use the weapons. The secret service sends James Bond to the Bahamas to once again save the world.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 09:54:32 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">913b54320b2f38cb52f562fca6895e41b952fd52b517cbf947632276c3bac3ad</guid></item><item><title>The World Is Not Enough</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/the-world-is-not-enough/#dts-hd-ma-51-dd-51</link><description>Greed, revenge, world dominance and high-tech terrorism – it's all in a day's work for Bond, who's on a mission to protect a beautiful oil heiress from a notorious terrorist. In a race against time that culminates in a dramatic submarine showdown, Bond works to defuse the international power struggle that has the world's oil supply hanging in the balance.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 09:54:32 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">86c244eed598ea2dfff4e0f54b0de7913a1f9847c606f8373e4b23c76ae8f8a9</guid></item><item><title>The Ghazi Attack</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/the-ghazi-attack/#atmos</link><description>India’s first underwater war film tries to decode the mystery behind the sinking of Pakistani submarine PNS Ghazi during the Indo-Pak war of 1971.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 09:31:14 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">6d04f34b7e5667e394cc9600fdb08b4f507ae7e165e78cda3d358f5b7fe25074</guid></item><item><title>Race to Witch Mountain</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/race-to-witch-mountain/#dts-hd-ma-51-dd-51</link><description>A taxi driver gets more than he bargained for when he picks up two teen runaways. Not only does the pair possess supernatural powers, but they're also trying desperately to escape people who have made them their targets.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 09:31:14 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">1014b209cc7a4a70f3de4ca2dc14fa8015176a9e0f8e54fea0934bd3e7ef2048</guid></item><item><title>Skyrunners</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/skyrunners/#dd-51</link><description>Tyler and his brother find an alien ship which makes Tyler appear older and gives him other abilities. This turns his high school life upside down, and may enable him to help his older brother's love life. After he is abducted by beings who intend to takeover Earth, he must depend on his inept and lovelorn brother to rescue him.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 09:31:14 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">128183fd502ea76f30520d9ee9d4ac35c0bae3687ec428ed0d4f00cb9fddbe2d</guid></item><item><title>A View to a Kill</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/a-view-to-a-kill/#dts-hd-ma-51-dd-51</link><description>A newly-developed microchip designed by Zorin Industries for the British Government that can survive the electromagnetic radiation caused by a nuclear explosion has landed in the hands of the KGB. James Bond must find out how and why. His suspicions soon lead him to big industry leader Max Zorin who forms a plan to destroy his only competition in Silicon Valley by triggering a massive earthquake in the San Francisco Bay.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 09:22:22 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">deac3f564ea1161c66a4e8146213bda01b0dba55a43039a927a324d3fd89e752</guid></item><item><title>Baaghi 2</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/baaghi-2/#dd-51</link><description /><pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 09:22:22 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">b4638725aff45cdf67eef03ddf8326b9e698921a3427b67e5a67adacb11159f4</guid></item><item><title>Bhuj: The Pride of India</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/bhuj-the-pride-of-india/#dd-51</link><description>Set in the backdrop of the 1971 Indo-Pakistan War, the film tells the story of the IAF Squadron Leader Vijay Karnik, and his bravery, patriotism and determination.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 09:22:22 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">deba3e7505e10be4851ffb2edd9c330828741038d7bae7db470af3eff5ab2180</guid></item><item><title>Casino Royale</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/casino-royale/#dts-hd-ma-51-dd-51</link><description>Le Chiffre, a banker to the world's terrorists, is scheduled to participate in a high-stakes poker game in Montenegro, where he intends to use his winnings to establish his financial grip on the terrorist market. M sends Bond—on his maiden mission as a 00 Agent—to attend this game and prevent Le Chiffre from winning. With the help of Vesper Lynd and Felix Leiter, Bond enters the most important poker game in his already dangerous career.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 09:22:22 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">4d79ba37479319995fda027cb78e1c1763311d4538aad80b8dd9741b88b8c558</guid></item><item><title>Code Red</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/code-red/#dd-51</link><description>A female doctor struggling to find her daughter after a long lost World War II biological weapon explodes on a U.S. military base in Bulgaria, turning people into mutant zombies.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 09:22:22 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">6d68b2d5da391772dfba4edfffd81ad057a9cc1aa6544f749db01aaef2765d46</guid></item><item><title>Cold Pursuit</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/cold-pursuit/#atmos-dd-51</link><description>The quiet family life of Nels Coxman, a snowplow driver, is upended after his son's murder. Nels begins a vengeful hunt for Viking, the drug lord he holds responsible for the killing, eliminating Viking's associates one by one. As Nels draws closer to Viking, his actions bring even more unexpected and violent consequences, as he proves that revenge is all in the execution.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 09:22:22 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">7abf78f99a3a4582611a669e34e27ca7ebde7532a7ff948d31779426c2acd48f</guid></item><item><title>Dhoom</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/dhoom/#dts-hd-ma-51</link><description>A gang of bikers headed by the cool-headed and arrogant Kabir is on a robbing spree in Mumbai. They rob establishments and then zip away on their superbikes. ACP Jai Dixit is the case in-charge and he recruits a bumbling bike mechanic and racer named Ali to chase the gang on a bike and help Jai nab them. Kabir accepts the challenge, and pulls off another robbery amidst a function. This causes Jai and Ali to call it off. Jai resigns from the police force and Ali goes back to his daily job. Meanwhile Kabir has lost one of his team members and recruits Ali for their final job in Goa. The action shifts from the congested Mumbai traffic to the sunny Goa for the final showdown between cops and robbers.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 09:22:22 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">d119557410cc2fc9f403483df4a024991147f0dd360106c85e5726286ec17225</guid></item><item><title>Dhoom 2</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/dhoom-2/#dts-hd-ma-51</link><description>Jai and Ali return, this time on the trail of an international thief who steals priceless artifacts and has chosen Mumbai as his next target.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 09:22:22 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">f1506a51f7927a283d0ebea423cdd4ac1ccfbcc36de638dca4b08a55924a586a</guid></item><item><title>Dhoom 3</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/dhoom-3/#dts-hd-ma-51</link><description>To avenge his father's death, a circus entertainer trained in magic and acrobatics turns thief to take down a corrupt bank in Chicago. Two cops from Mumbai are assigned to the case.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 09:22:22 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">5ee427bf14f3c26f55eb6c4f248dab8fcc9edd7e4bc554497552d70155d6d2e3</guid></item><item><title>Diamonds Are Forever</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/diamonds-are-forever/#dts-hd-ma-51-dd-51</link><description>Diamonds are stolen only to be sold again in the international market. James Bond infiltrates a smuggling mission to find out who's guilty. The mission takes him to Las Vegas where Bond meets his archenemy Blofeld.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 09:22:22 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">35514dc1ec0066a317e3e5134ba417333015d85f301351c0c6e524dfe15c5a61</guid></item><item><title>Die Another Day</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/die-another-day/#dts-hd-ma-51-dd-51</link><description>James Bond is sent to investigate the connection between a North Korean terrorist and a diamond mogul, who is funding the development of an international space weapon.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 09:22:22 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">8f3a10e7a7f1001cb6e207664547a6ca780ac02f9658ce71150e36c6680891f6</guid></item><item><title>Dr. No</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/dr-no/#dts-hd-ma-51-dd-51</link><description>In the film that launched the James Bond saga, Agent 007 battles mysterious Dr. No, a scientific genius bent on destroying the U.S. space program. As the countdown to disaster begins, Bond must go to Jamaica, where he encounters beautiful Honey Ryder, to confront a megalomaniacal villain in his massive island headquarters.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 09:22:22 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">3ba79998bfc2c143da1697cc2234d1712786ccfe8d5f5f490ec4e00e0a748ce6</guid></item><item><title>For Your Eyes Only</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/for-your-eyes-only/#dts-hd-ma-51-dd-51</link><description>A British spy ship has sunk and on board was a hi-tech encryption device. James Bond is sent to find the device that holds British launching instructions before the enemy Soviets get to it first.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 09:22:22 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">d3479ac4340a239282456d3a83dc73563c9a96929e4e6d6d0dc67829e296cfd4</guid></item><item><title>From Russia with Love</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/from-russia-with-love/#dts-hd-ma-51-dd-51</link><description>Agent 007 is back in the second installment of the James Bond series, this time battling a secret crime organization known as SPECTRE. Russians Rosa Klebb and Kronsteen are out to snatch a decoding device known as the Lektor, using the ravishing Tatiana to lure Bond into helping them. Bond willingly travels to meet Tatiana in Istanbul, where he must rely on his wits to escape with his life in a series of deadly encounters with the enemy.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 09:22:22 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">4c9a890ac1bd31d2c09919feaa38cd35c5323b0da4fbddea8a406ea48b39b2f0</guid></item><item><title>Goldfinger</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/goldfinger/#dts-hd-ma-51-dd-51</link><description>Special agent 007 comes face to face with one of the most notorious villains of all time, and now he must outwit and outgun the powerful tycoon to prevent him from cashing in on a devious scheme to raid Fort Knox -- and obliterate the world's economy.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 09:22:22 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">4f5dd5cff9305793e4f8e952864ceb193bbf6b754938728d6ec5e5564cd926bc</guid></item><item><title>Licence to Kill</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/licence-to-kill/#dts-hd-ma-51-dd-51</link><description>After capturing the notorious drug lord Franz Sanchez, Bond's close friend and former CIA agent Felix Leiter is left for dead and his wife is murdered. Bond goes rogue and seeks vengeance on those responsible, as he infiltrates Sanchez's organization from the inside.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 09:22:22 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">defe9a079121e907ed001f50f925fbf96e71a2c5957484be84b14a9235e013c8</guid></item><item><title>Holiday</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/holiday_273886/#dts-hd-ma-51</link><description>A soldier on vacation finds himself hunting down a terrorist.  A military officer attempts to hunt down a terrorist, destroy a terrorist gang and deactivate the sleeper cells under its command.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 03:26:06 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">b3ba0fff749b448b4ae74e951b5a59602f8f6f0465841f7ee46418aa59fad02a</guid></item><item><title>The Sixth Secret</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/the-sixth-secret/#dd-51</link><description>At a late-night seance, attended by twelve people, the medium announces that five secrets will be revealed before midnight. There might, however, be one more - the darkest of them all.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 01:53:17 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">1e4d85cd21bef26c85fd6f7bc1e71e482af6e0d0d61925dddec99443ac7b49fc</guid></item><item><title>Big Beasts</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/big-beasts/#season-1</link><description>Travel from freezing poles to tropical rainforests to meet nature’s most captivating giants, who prove being big comes with enormous challenges.</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2023 22:33:31 -0000</pubDate><category>TV</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">f419f16fadcb61c982b3285ec266eab3642d1283d2371fbf4d0ad55d77078164</guid></item><item><title>Crater</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/crater/#dd-atmos</link><description>After the death of his father, a boy growing up on a lunar mining colony takes a trip to explore a legendary crater, along with his four best friends, prior to being permanently relocated to another planet.</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2023 22:28:34 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">c71f66440b41bd26903e42e58c54b96d3a09b182e52c53f458d4965a4dc74e72</guid></item><item><title>57 Seconds</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/57-seconds/#dd-51</link><description>When a tech blogger lands an interview with a tech guru and stops an attack on him, he finds a mysterious ring that takes him back 57 seconds into the past.</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2023 19:44:57 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">aba3723fdfb07b055778e76f5f68989e8b6dcb7e8297f390e583069c65ebf401</guid></item><item><title>The Game Plan</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/the-game-plan/#dd-51</link><description>Bachelor football star Joe Kingman seems to have it all. He is wealthy and carefree, and his team is on the way to capturing a championship. Suddenly, he is tackled by some unexpected news: He has a young daughter, the result of a last fling with his ex-wife. Joe must learn to balance his personal and professional lives with the needs of his child.</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2023 19:44:57 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">2e0fe1bddbc3b7fcc7135a80f423946ea3b7315eb1dc9c07bc226fc1608a9720</guid></item><item><title>Talk to Me</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/talk-to-me/#atmos</link><description>When a group of friends discover how to conjure spirits using an embalmed hand, they become hooked on the new thrill, until one of them goes too far and unleashes terrifying supernatural forces.</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2023 19:44:57 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">460d7a2c0b4da08ba3d59fbdff0543f4cab4f0b49101993537d0b8f1758b22f3</guid></item><item><title>Talk to Me</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/halcyon888/talk-to-me/#atmos</link><description>When a group of friends discover how to conjure spirits using an embalmed hand, they become hooked on the new thrill, until one of them goes too far and unleashes terrifying supernatural forces.</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2023 16:12:10 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>halcyon888</category><guid isPermaLink="false">284839a31045e70663372616ce85ddbf63151460c18a0fa5da8ae28a8140e182</guid></item><item><title>The Black Phone</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/halcyon888/the-black-phone/#atmos</link><description>Finney Blake, a shy but clever 13-year-old boy, is abducted by a sadistic killer and trapped in a soundproof basement where screaming is of little use. When a disconnected phone on the wall begins to ring, Finney discovers that he can hear the voices of the killer’s previous victims. And they are dead set on making sure that what happened to them doesn’t happen to Finney.</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2023 15:38:43 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>halcyon888</category><guid isPermaLink="false">747c8f846d5da7ae5789c80b874f06209ae39c7e39e5f1d3c5dd77e20e254abb</guid></item><item><title>Talk to Me</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/t1g8rsfan/talk-to-me/#atmos</link><description>When a group of friends discover how to conjure spirits using an embalmed hand, they become hooked on the new thrill, until one of them goes too far and unleashes terrifying supernatural forces.</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2023 13:06:13 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>t1g8rsfan</category><guid isPermaLink="false">53dfab8f114bda4b5b9dc73157ba37362c5032067d85c44d2da612c08b5cb1ce</guid></item><item><title>Bhediya</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/bhediya/#dd-51</link><description>Inspired by legendary folklore rooted in Arunachal Pradesh, Bhediya tells the story of Bhaskar, a man who gets bitten by a mythical wolf and begins to transform into the creature himself. As Bhaskar and his ragtag buddies try to find answers, he is worried that the monster in him will wipe out human existence in the local town.</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2023 10:34:33 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">33c56efec27cfbecf283fdb9345fc990a756f318ae6eabe54ad61433ba4003d7</guid></item><item><title>Don</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/don/#dts-hd-ma-51</link><description>Don, a rich twelve-year-old, is kicked out of school. He is send to another school where he has difficulties fitting in.</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2023 10:34:33 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">284d7f953df0dba960a196fd67746b075eadde773d0966c7350c4e0ec0f4f535</guid></item><item><title>Kahaani</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/kahaani/#truehd-51</link><description>Pregnant and alone in the city of Kolkata, a woman begins a relentless search for her missing husband, only to find that nothing is what it seems.</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2023 10:34:33 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">59e98d5be4155c99bd988e79c9aa714927452556fbe913a33364f9b552585e79</guid></item><item><title>Kesari</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/kesari/#dts-hd-ma-51</link><description>In 1897, an army of 21 Sikhs battles 10,000 Afghans to prevent the Saragarhi Fort from being taken down.</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2023 10:34:33 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">3ad404d16bb76e8e364b1602dcccb7d90227564fd2d2c69e4c95d5d05d02195f</guid></item><item><title>Wonder</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/wonder/#truehd-71</link><description>The story of August Pullman – a boy with facial differences – who enters fifth grade, attending a mainstream elementary school for the first time.</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2023 10:34:33 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">5f5d0a78cbe89d0210498f50e46aaad243910d501901781b82d7ffb9a6b1d1f2</guid></item><item><title>Reptile</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/halcyon888/reptile/#dd-atmos</link><description>Following the brutal murder of a young real estate agent, a hardened detective attempts to uncover the truth in a case where nothing is as it seems, and by doing so dismantles the illusions in his own life.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 19:37:34 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>halcyon888</category><guid isPermaLink="false">31ea174d8aef51c1e2852cfaea3d5786ba74b2c31ac9106e8e1f3017536745bd</guid></item><item><title>Gen V</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/halcyon888/gen-v/#season-1-episodes-1-3</link><description>At America's only college for superheroes, gifted students put their moral boundaries to the test, competing for the university's top ranking, and a chance to join The Seven, Vought International's elite superhero team. When the school's dark secrets come to light, they must decide what kind of heroes they want to become.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 19:37:34 -0000</pubDate><category>TV</category><category>halcyon888</category><guid isPermaLink="false">a62992af1db44c14d174196f70fbcba7cb9663763433988b7318073fe624b9b3</guid></item><item><title>Heist 88</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/heist-88/#dd-51</link><description>A criminal mastermind recruits a group of young bank employees to steal 80 million dollars in one of the largest bank heist in US history.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 18:52:12 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">f5890231f5a22295a40b9b2f89bf887961099c74eca3f756258025a10a65ef9d</guid></item><item><title>Highway</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/highway/#dts-hd-ma-51</link><description>Right before her wedding, a young woman finds herself abducted and held for ransom. As the initial days pass, she begins to develop a strange bond with her kidnapper.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 18:52:12 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">175f30652c5321e4e53c337e052c9dcd681c2bd4fab1d5efe7f18834cacde512</guid></item><item><title>Nowhere</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/nowhere/#dd-atmos</link><description>A young pregnant woman named Mia escapes from a country at war by hiding in a maritime container aboard a cargo ship. After a violent storm, Mia gives birth to the child while lost at sea, where she must fight to survive.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 18:52:12 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">7fb8504bc1091411e1d1bb985554b965338e620551a1bf2e8fd080402e3ccc7d</guid></item><item><title>Reptile</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/reptile/#dd-atmos</link><description>Following the brutal murder of a young real estate agent, a hardened detective attempts to uncover the truth in a case where nothing is as it seems, and by doing so dismantles the illusions in his own life.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 18:52:12 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">9b28d357b34452be9eb7c1f43418336c5f99656c6bb76d5dd3b3c9d430fb669d</guid></item><item><title>Wanted</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/wanted_22717/#dd-51</link><description>Radhe is a hardcore gangster. A sharpshooter with a sharp brain, he works for Gani Bhai, the dreaded Mafioso, but on his own terms. Totally fearless, Radhe single handedly eliminates Gani Bhai's enemies one by one; making more enemies than he bargained for.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 18:52:12 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">318685b4231a974b0167e15c7c7b2290bdc43dd6077935e26913313570e6105c</guid></item><item><title>Choona</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/choona/#season-1</link><description>When an unlikely group of misfits discovers a common enemy in the same ruthless yet superstitious politician, they plot a heist to exact revenge.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 18:52:12 -0000</pubDate><category>TV</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">a0277286c0f187b29026bf59e49a48a4c6fd759f93e52e4b4836659c8263c3d1</guid></item><item><title>Prey</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/t1g8rsfan/prey/#atmos-dd-atmos</link><description>When danger threatens her camp, the fierce and highly skilled Comanche warrior Naru sets out to protect her people. But the prey she stalks turns out to be a highly evolved alien predator with a technically advanced arsenal.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 18:29:07 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>t1g8rsfan</category><guid isPermaLink="false">1662ac34afc647ace463b343d9f2139ee61603c68ba97408154e6eb0b50969bd</guid></item><item><title>The Continental: From the World of John Wick</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/halcyon888/the-continental-from-the-world-of-john-wick/#season-1-episode-2</link><description>Winston Scott is roped into a world of assassins and must make things right after his brother's attack on the Continental hotel.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 17:17:15 -0000</pubDate><category>TV</category><category>halcyon888</category><guid isPermaLink="false">45993bc5323f9e6e34490d2150f9551186d34d79d7718496ce209c9c6912c39a</guid></item><item><title>The Wheel of Time</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/halcyon888/the-wheel-of-time/#season-2-episodes-1-5-7</link><description>Follow Moiraine, a member of the shadowy and influential all-female organization called the “Aes Sedai” as she embarks on a dangerous, world-spanning journey with five young men and women. Moiraine believes one of them might be the reincarnation of an incredibly powerful individual, whom prophecies say will either save humanity or destroy it.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 17:17:15 -0000</pubDate><category>TV</category><category>halcyon888</category><guid isPermaLink="false">851b1d69c0175b463cb4344e96ff7f3fc606d5a7e9e72694d3bd8f82c8318bd8</guid></item><item><title>U-571</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/t1g8rsfan/u-571/#dts-hd-ma-51</link><description>In the midst of World War II, the battle under the sea rages and the Nazis have the upper hand as the Allies are unable to crack their war codes. However, after a wrecked U-boat sends out an SOS signal, the Allies realise this is their chance to seize the 'enigma coding machine'.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 13:52:15 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>t1g8rsfan</category><guid isPermaLink="false">2735c6998467e1891593a3f2f5b1154fa432db4f7e059afbb4ceafae328cb147</guid></item><item><title>The Machine</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/t1g8rsfan/the-machine/#dts-hd-ma-51-dd</link><description>Bert Kreischer faces a familial crisis and the arrival of his estranged father when the ghost of his booze-soaked past arrives: a murderous mobster hellbent on kidnapping Bert back to the motherland to atone for his crimes. Together, he and his father must retrace the steps of his younger self in the midst of a war between a sociopathic crime family while they attempt to find common ground.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 13:51:16 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>t1g8rsfan</category><guid isPermaLink="false">21443143dd037c02c708cbfef811ee13be4902c22d4fac1756c51d16f43fe653</guid></item><item><title>How to Blow Up a Pipeline</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/how-to-blow-up-a-pipeline/#dts-hd-ma-51</link><description>A crew of young environmental activists execute a daring mission to sabotage an oil pipeline.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 01:17:45 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">2a45cb9f5ab9b2b2ec5e74aa04cf1dd0da86d1efaf4de95cd6d8aa3df1db5666</guid></item><item><title>Sorcerer</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/sorcerer/#dts-hd-ma-51</link><description>Four men from different parts of the globe, all hiding from their pasts in the same remote South American town, agree to risk their lives transporting several cases of dynamite (which is so old that it is dripping unstable nitroglycerin) across dangerous jungle terrain.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 21:21:08 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">a5e3f0bc210a71963cdf8b19586a2538876c942df6da91bd668a1d712970f9a0</guid></item><item><title>Aged</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/aged/#dd-51</link><description>After taking a temporary job as a caregiver, a young woman realizes her employer and the house have a dangerous, dark past.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 19:45:52 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">34ce1d71dc7bebe836985ebe3eb36aa4cdeb64c8713f9d54ec882565582df6cd</guid></item><item><title>Batman: The Doom That Came to Gotham</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/batman-the-doom-that-came-to-gotham/#dts-hd-ma-51-dd-51</link><description>Explorer Bruce Wayne accidentally unleashes an ancient evil, and returns to Gotham after being away for two decades. There, Batman battles Lovecraftian supernatural forces and encounters allies and enemies such as Green Arrow, Ra's al Ghul, Mr. Freeze, Killer Croc, Two-Face and James Gordon.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 19:45:52 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">a7ad2fd845be9503dd3997eb34877efbd2fb31e90a93c538436e1b820779952c</guid></item><item><title>Mummies</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/mummies/#dd-51</link><description>Through a series of unfortunate events, three mummies end up in present-day London and embark on a wacky and hilarious journey in search of an old ring belonging to the Royal Family, stolen by ambitious archaeologist Lord Carnaby.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 19:45:52 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">bf0fb1f6c79dd862f98111dd5df0d7ac82f3f298ed34759de5edb9a98703f534</guid></item><item><title>Force 2</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/force-2/#dts-hd-ma-51</link><description>ACP Yashvardhan teams up RAW Agent KK to bring down the master mind terrorist, Shiv.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 18:48:58 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">671da869746d868be51bd34ef8bd9a9c68d43f49f41b4f9cc071ee913529b95f</guid></item><item><title>Panic Room</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/panic-room/#dts-hd-ma-51-dd-51</link><description>Trapped in their New York brownstone's panic room, a hidden chamber built as a sanctuary in the event of break-ins, newly divorced Meg Altman and her young daughter Sarah play a deadly game of cat-and-mouse with three intruders - Burnham, Raoul and Junior - during a brutal home invasion. But the room itself is the focal point because what the intruders really want is inside it.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 18:48:58 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">0ee3db3e7673c84ad2a803113c568586e979071c37258f81d71bf59ab4be2998</guid></item><item><title>Shootout at Wadala</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/shootout-at-wadala/#dts-hd-ma-71</link><description>The first-ever registered encounter by the Mumbai Police, which took place on November 1, 1982.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 18:48:58 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">03a12a7934632db6ba4fb618a9d415a456f3d29b69a4732f164c3b8c7e37e34c</guid></item><item><title>Thugs of Hindostan</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/thugs-of-hindostan/#atmos</link><description>After the British company’s officer Clive takes over the kingdom of Mirza, Princess Zafira and Khudabaksh aka Azaad form a band of rebel pirates who swear to defeat the English officer and win their freedom back. The British Company in return, hire the wily thug Firangi track Azaad’s gang and thwart his plans.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 18:48:58 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">c580ac595318a324d1bc9de66c2dc40e23e444a1d345df1caae4ff801725d1b6</guid></item><item><title>Prey</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/halcyon888/prey/#atmos</link><description>When danger threatens her camp, the fierce and highly skilled Comanche warrior Naru sets out to protect her people. But the prey she stalks turns out to be a highly evolved alien predator with a technically advanced arsenal.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 17:52:07 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>halcyon888</category><guid isPermaLink="false">0851a3eb200e4ecf6747e513bbb4f4a98d27ff4bc1a97e18d0636c4325fcd629</guid></item><item><title>Invasion</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/halcyon888/invasion/#season-2-episodes-5-6</link><description>Earth is visited by an alien species that threatens humanity’s existence. Events unfold in real time through the eyes of five ordinary people across the globe as they struggle to make sense of the chaos unraveling around them.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 17:31:18 -0000</pubDate><category>TV</category><category>halcyon888</category><guid isPermaLink="false">d4191866aef0a5fd6a4211f842c394b4bb10fbf9753f842f371bb10ccc4781ab</guid></item><item><title>Ghayal Once Again</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/ghayal-once-again/#dts-hd-ma-51</link><description>Ajay Mehra (from previous Ghayal-1990), after finishing off his life sentence, starts a newspaper called Satyakam. Still dealing with the haunting trauma of losing his loved ones, Ajay manages to make a credible name for himself in investigative journalism. Working with a strange team of RTI activists, ex-criminals and ilk; and even stranger ways of unearthing and presenting truth, Ajay Mehra has earned quite a fan following among the youths, who finds his fearless and unforgiving approach in dealing with all kinds of sociopaths very inspiring.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 09:00:09 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">c19dce63e95f0c31f24b6cf67d638416be7c7f596b23cee06821b2137a359c5a</guid></item><item><title>Last of the Dogmen</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/last-of-the-dogmen/#dts-hd-ma-51</link><description>A Montana bounty hunter is sent into the wilderness to track three escaped prisoners. Instead he sees something that puzzles him. Later with a female Native Indian history professor, he returns to find some answers.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 09:00:09 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">5dc266f54b078024a4162c3dd7252cce38157e202a28a0de055c09e7cca3d04e</guid></item><item><title>Rustom</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/rustom/#atmos</link><description>A naval officer is devastated to learn about his wife's extramarital affair with a rich businessman while he was away. He pays him a visit and shoots him to death, following which he surrenders himself but claims to be "not guilty" in the court, much to the surprise of the businessman's sister and the officers dealing with his case.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 09:00:09 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">3c16923adb280abe57b5328c5c8acd1d9a899cef73746b4598c49717d2149645</guid></item><item><title>Special 26</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/special-26/#dts-hd-ma-51</link><description>In the early 1980s in India, a group of con artists rob well-known businessmen and politicians by posing as officers of the Central Bureau of Intelligence or income tax officials. The gang stages fake raids during which they steal great amounts of money from their targets.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 09:00:09 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">0eb580ad790fe57f99cc5584bc500df75c826e9bc89c1db0278895eb116fa3e3</guid></item><item><title>Castlevania: Nocturne</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/castlevania-nocturne/#season-1</link><description>In the thick of the French Revolution, members of the so-called lower classes are rising up to fight inequality. Meanwhile, Richter Belmont senses a far grimmer and greater danger. He's picked up his family's long-held tradition of vampire hunting, a vocation that goes back almost as long as a vampiric life span (in other words, forever) but he's never seen anything quite like what he's witnessing now.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 09:00:09 -0000</pubDate><category>TV</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">e236d7cbff980796245db6b1d28ab63a555e57c657857c81af475d46385cc939</guid></item><item><title>Gran Turismo</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/t1g8rsfan/gran-turismo/#dd</link><description>The ultimate wish-fulfillment tale of a teenage Gran Turismo player whose gaming skills won him a series of Nissan competitions to become an actual professional racecar driver.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 03:14:08 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>t1g8rsfan</category><guid isPermaLink="false">2b8fa727889bfca05da6d5152e8c8082497035a525cdf77c68bec555c14f270e</guid></item><item><title>Loki</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/loki/#season-1</link><description>After stealing the Tesseract during the events of “Avengers: Endgame,” an alternate version of Loki is brought to the mysterious Time Variance Authority, a bureaucratic organization that exists outside of time and space and monitors the timeline. They give Loki a choice: face being erased from existence due to being a “time variant” or help fix the timeline and stop a greater threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 22:40:41 -0000</pubDate><category>TV</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">e446dfaa538bd48caa5ab7381a2849df6be1bb7dbf7bb405a6daa44018e73f18</guid></item><item><title>Action Jackson</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/action-jackson/#dd-51</link><description>A man meets his lookalike, who's not just a killer of evil, but also a kind hearted man. Together, they team up to fight against a dreaded gangster.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 20:01:18 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">eba04ef99c5b8417097266e09dfa6e0998839b75da925a9b6a924ad75e11f14a</guid></item><item><title>Arjun Patiala</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/arjun-patiala/#dd-51</link><description>This spoof comedy narrates the story of a cop Arjun Patiala and his sidekick Onidda Singh. Together, will they be able to accomplish their mission of a crime-free town with their goofy style of policing?</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 20:01:18 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">f39ba43ece89f4f2d50edc6b655347b4923696ac27336d247ae1d85a3b3c1342</guid></item><item><title>Bunty Aur Babli</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/bunty-aur-babli/#dd-51</link><description>Bunty and Babli are two avid dreamers. Two free souls born into caged small town realities. They grow weary of being two specks on the horizon. They desire the horizon itself.And so they pack their aspirations in worn out bags, whip a scarf of confidence around their proud necks and set forth. On a journey across the length and breadth of the country, spinning circles around the people they meet.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 20:01:18 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">b296c4d02cc1c4a7a0a55226e7df9218a17dc63bbdff875b33295af26c87636a</guid></item><item><title>Bunty Aur Babli 2</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/bunty-aur-babli-2/#dd-51</link><description>Bunty and Babli are forced out of retirement as a new pair of cons emerge, doing robberies in their name with their trademark sigil across India.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 20:01:18 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">f8053d82f22355266f6f06b2c7023edcc2273581bb86d8f74e0b27354f19d599</guid></item><item><title>Overhaul</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/overhaul/#dd-atmos</link><description>When truck racer Roger loses everything, he receives a tempting but dangerous offer: to work as the getaway driver for a gang of thieves.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 20:01:18 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">7d6211441835d1a7dc72a2a4056fa5483a2dd173f130d7eb7837cacd0c52c908</guid></item><item><title>R... Rajkumar</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/r-rajkumar/#dd-51</link><description>Rajkumar, an aimless youth, works for a drug baron and is sent to kill a rival dealer. His life is changed forever when he meets Chanda, and has no idea she is the adopted daughter of the man he is supposed to kill.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 20:01:18 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">92e1c76c963cccb8912017e4670b6b97c24ae411641f8fddf5fec80fac46bac4</guid></item><item><title>Street Flow 2</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/street-flow-2/#dd-51</link><description>Struggling to overcome cycles of betrayal, revenge and violence, the Traoré brothers continue to fight for a brighter future in a seedy Paris suburb.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 20:01:18 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">ad5e857ccbcbb594b74600c9d7bd6672fd5c943bae1351a7bed4d7fb9c320eba</guid></item><item><title>Veer-Zaara</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/veer-zaara/#dd-51</link><description>Squadron Leader Veer Pratap Singh, a pilot in the Indian air force, rescues the stranded Zaara, a woman from Pakistan, following a bus accident, and their lives are forever bound.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 20:01:18 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">7e869178008dc5f9c48f25db517a50a24d18971bb8fc429e62c580d540c26879</guid></item><item><title>The Strain</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/the-strain/#season-1</link><description>A high concept thriller that tells the story of Dr. Ephraim Goodweather, the head of the Center for Disease Control Canary Team in New York City. He and his team are called upon to investigate a mysterious viral outbreak with hallmarks of an ancient and evil strain of vampirism. As the strain spreads, Eph, his team, and an assembly of everyday New Yorkers, wage war for the fate of humanity itself.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 20:01:18 -0000</pubDate><category>TV</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">257f8cf4f4cc6c83c86bbdc0da9bf69b8c55aa24a6adaecd5f4603e9b86a4fa7</guid></item><item><title>The Strain</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/the-strain/#season-2</link><description>A high concept thriller that tells the story of Dr. Ephraim Goodweather, the head of the Center for Disease Control Canary Team in New York City. He and his team are called upon to investigate a mysterious viral outbreak with hallmarks of an ancient and evil strain of vampirism. As the strain spreads, Eph, his team, and an assembly of everyday New Yorkers, wage war for the fate of humanity itself.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 20:01:18 -0000</pubDate><category>TV</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">4b7f129947fc9cbce903a046a97898d24ddf502f2caabbf21bf4efe31eba9199</guid></item><item><title>The Strain</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/the-strain/#season-3</link><description>A high concept thriller that tells the story of Dr. Ephraim Goodweather, the head of the Center for Disease Control Canary Team in New York City. He and his team are called upon to investigate a mysterious viral outbreak with hallmarks of an ancient and evil strain of vampirism. As the strain spreads, Eph, his team, and an assembly of everyday New Yorkers, wage war for the fate of humanity itself.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 20:01:18 -0000</pubDate><category>TV</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">6230fd2b35ce6c483f695f98bcba5d11a5e40d0591a6a71eeec6a2721ab84449</guid></item><item><title>The Strain</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/the-strain/#season-4</link><description>A high concept thriller that tells the story of Dr. Ephraim Goodweather, the head of the Center for Disease Control Canary Team in New York City. He and his team are called upon to investigate a mysterious viral outbreak with hallmarks of an ancient and evil strain of vampirism. As the strain spreads, Eph, his team, and an assembly of everyday New Yorkers, wage war for the fate of humanity itself.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 20:01:18 -0000</pubDate><category>TV</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">96054574ddf8f5213027d54040879c81b7736554ebb793a490e5f27bd5895576</guid></item><item><title>Ahsoka</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/halcyon888/ahsoka/#season-1-episodes-5-7</link><description>Former Jedi Knight Ahsoka Tano investigates an emerging threat to a vulnerable galaxy.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 18:59:48 -0000</pubDate><category>TV</category><category>halcyon888</category><guid isPermaLink="false">b2b4727c041136144f68f91adcbc23d4518591506a96e97bc3f554d2ae01559d</guid></item><item><title>Prey</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/prey_766507/#atmos</link><description>When danger threatens her camp, the fierce and highly skilled Comanche warrior Naru sets out to protect her people. But the prey she stalks turns out to be a highly evolved alien predator with a technically advanced arsenal.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 18:02:19 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">a5a3ac2dee7d5f5111889ddf87f3b3b77136ab13a8dae841abb4cdfb8dd19e42</guid></item><item><title>3: The Dale Earnhardt Story</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/3-the-dale-earnhardt-story/#dd-51</link><description>A biopic of NASCAR legend Dale Earnhardt, Sr., documenting the driver's career from his earliest days onward and also looking at the family he built along the way. Earnhardt's death in 2001 rocked the sport, but his seven championships and 76 wins made an impact on NASCAR forever.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 10:13:44 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">5c83da0891167baa6690ac0a9064eea18f97d92fb95336624ede24c229820cf5</guid></item><item><title>Mission Kashmir</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/mission-kashmir/#dd-51</link><description>A police officer adopts the son and sole survivor of a family he has massacred while pursuing a terrorist. After some time the foster son finds out what the stepfather did.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 10:13:44 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">fa197649c4ee25995e4259d2a6ca9c7cd5b2e736d808370b9a33cf7d0da0e551</guid></item><item><title>Tandav</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/tandav/#season-1</link><description>Tandav is the coming together of different worlds under the gamut of politics. It is a dramatic take of the powerplay between people at the highest level where they get overthrown by others to secure their position. Young and upcoming student politicians are also featured and we get to see where their future is headed in this dark abyss of politics.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 10:13:44 -0000</pubDate><category>TV</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">bdca2a93c7e077acf6d304908e5eb2c7421fe45ea74993f4ad6b01f1577b116c</guid></item><item><title>Gran Turismo</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/halcyon888/gran-turismo/#dd</link><description>The ultimate wish-fulfillment tale of a teenage Gran Turismo player whose gaming skills won him a series of Nissan competitions to become an actual professional racecar driver.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 02:21:40 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>halcyon888</category><guid isPermaLink="false">6979473a0ef7e1083f0da2156d4e1fa6422fe569b2adfb55d71904aaa5c338e9</guid></item><item><title>U-571</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/u-571/#dts-hd-ma-51</link><description>In the midst of World War II, the battle under the sea rages and the Nazis have the upper hand as the Allies are unable to crack their war codes. However, after a wrecked U-boat sends out an SOS signal, the Allies realise this is their chance to seize the 'enigma coding machine'.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 02:06:37 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">384f79331dfa32ea4db23a37ff0348fa3c40676cebaf9c034c94f835b1674f91</guid></item><item><title>Rocky Aur Rani Kii Prem Kahaani</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/rocky-aur-rani-kii-prem-kahaani/#dd-51</link><description>Gym-freak brat Rocky falls in love with Rani, who comes from a well-educated Bengali family. Being from polar opposite worlds, the two decide to switch their families to adjust to each other's cultures and backgrounds and to know if their marriage will survive. Rocky and Rani are trapped in a world where they are united by love but divided by families and the ultimate question is will they fit in?</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 01:15:13 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">f35a6ba59f9b3363a9bbb097d1991939f016f247c03a3d5e21cc9ffc07c5ab3e</guid></item><item><title>Vikram Vedha</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/vikram-vedha_851783/#dd-51</link><description>Vikram, an honest officer with the Lucknow police, is on a mission to find and eliminate gangster Vedha. However, when Vedha surrenders himself to the police and starts narrating stories to Vikram, it blurs the lines between good and evil. Vedha questions Vikram's righteousness while the latter believes he is fair and just. But is he?</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 01:15:13 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">dace2d0ec882a5dd65f994554711ab5e2307f8ba8c717e0f845c43479ec55964</guid></item><item><title>Black Knight</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/black-knight/#dd-51</link><description>Martin Lawrence plays Jamal, an employee in Medieval World amusement park. After nearly drowning in the moat, he awakens to find himself in 14th century England.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2023 19:57:52 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">a92823c0e3fbd75bd43c32b22b8c849ceb2a78d48f55ff5c65559b043a480e80</guid></item><item><title>Golmaal Returns</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/golmaal-returns/#dd-51</link><description>Golmaal Returns, the much-awaited follow-up to the uproariously comical smash-hit Golmaal, arrives with a renewed star power, chartbusting music and more laughter than ever before!</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2023 19:57:52 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">eb1b7a2778a57f6aa7ea3abbd207730caa2475e9fb0dbee023eab1f02d3e14f6</guid></item><item><title>Gran Turismo</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/gran-turismo/#dd-51</link><description>The ultimate wish-fulfillment tale of a teenage Gran Turismo player whose gaming skills won him a series of Nissan competitions to become an actual professional racecar driver.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2023 19:57:52 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">a978f75bb6e0fdbdd40491773fe429b35c686deeb2d85a74eabf642e28346b39</guid></item><item><title>Hum Tum</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/hum-tum/#dd-51</link><description>The encounters of two people who run into each other on several occasions under circumstances ranging from friendly to hostile to loving. Along many years and countless run-ins, the two despise each other, befriend each other, and fall in love with each other—in no particular order.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2023 19:57:52 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">7ff1ab222b266ba370662228e5d148c5afe4e3310cadf5560292e77912cbd9e4</guid></item><item><title>Redemption Day</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/redemption-day/#dd-51</link><description>When his wife is kidnapped by terrorists for ransom, veteran war hero Brad Paxton races against the clock to rescue her in a daring and deadly operation that pits him against powerful and dark forces.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2023 19:57:52 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">a97b6d6a27bff1833b24cf451ed2801e1a5071ba74a683a6844ba0457af73e84</guid></item><item><title>The Dark Knight Rises</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/halcyon888/the-dark-knight-rises/#dts-hd-ma-51</link><description>Following the death of District Attorney Harvey Dent, Batman assumes responsibility for Dent's crimes to protect the late attorney's reputation and is subsequently hunted by the Gotham City Police Department. Eight years later, Batman encounters the mysterious Selina Kyle and the villainous Bane, a new terrorist leader who overwhelms Gotham's finest. The Dark Knight resurfaces to protect a city that has branded him an enemy.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2023 00:51:35 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>halcyon888</category><guid isPermaLink="false">76dbde1c1bb56ad1c4e7fc72fc32d693bea6349aab1af452c0170572f79f053e</guid></item><item><title>The Last Dragon</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/the-last-dragon/#atmos-dts-hd-ma-71</link><description>A young man searches for the "master" to obtain the final level of martial arts mastery known as the glow. Along the way he must fight an evil martial arts expert and rescue a beautiful singer from an obsessed music promoter.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 18:17:23 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">4eb02aea817fa499db4b5b10a8526aeeade1bb9ee74765c4b79abaeef2da2255</guid></item><item><title>Bedurulanka 2012</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/bedurulanka-2012/#dd-51</link><description>Set in a small island village of Yedurulanka,  faces the looming uncertainties of 2012, Shiva, a pragmatic youngster along with his girlfriend Chithra and friends, devise a scheme to disprove the end of the world theory and expose the plan by the trio of fake god-men, to fleece the people.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 10:06:55 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">bf3e9c5f5f438d684f7e32a225b89bc1b45e44b86ecdc00cc73b0a3958701123</guid></item><item><title>Gold</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/gold/#dd-51</link><description>Set in 1948, the historic story of India's first Olympic medal post their independence.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 10:06:55 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">1815448c5b0690536993c39a56286b5260c65997cc7528903d5e55dc250272ac</guid></item><item><title>Good Newwz</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/good-newwz/#dd-51</link><description>Two couples with the same surnames pursue in-vitro fertilisation and wait for their upcoming babies. Trouble ensues when they find that the sperms of each couple have been mixed with each other.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 10:06:55 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">d21a6ea84fa7fa11b81454eb38c4da432946e9c40951506dbc6e77917450e49f</guid></item><item><title>It Follows</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/it-follows/#atmos</link><description>When carefree teenager Jay sleeps with her older boyfriend for the first time, she learns that she is the latest recipient of a fatal curse that is passed from victim to victim via sexual intercourse. Death, Jay learns, will creep inexorably toward her as either a friend or a stranger. Jay's friends don't believe her seemingly paranoid ravings, until they too begin to see the phantom assassins and band together to help her defend herself.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 10:06:55 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">88e718c759861ee3d40cd40b1ab6980c2bad0cc2de5130e915a0f9bed4b540d1</guid></item><item><title>Pagalpanti</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/pagalpanti/#dd-51</link><description>3 men, considered as losers in their lives by the people, plan to get rich along with their girlfriends by fooling 2 gangsters and robbing their money.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 10:06:55 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">8d3f081957a847f1258df87dbf692af5fc75a6399d6499fb1ad316724c70c106</guid></item><item><title>RDX: Robert Dony Xavier</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/rdx-robert-dony-xavier/#dd-51</link><description>Once-menacing, anger fueled, trained martial arts fighters Robert, Dony and Xavier settle down to peaceful lives, after a significant event prompts them. Fate orchestrates their reunion and return from exile to their fighting ways, when their history linger ominously and one of them faces a violent attack.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 10:06:55 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">48ab77d021fb3dff43ae97617c99814d054699032a0ec04e071ee84fccafae91</guid></item><item><title>Rohan at the Louvre</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/rohan-at-the-louvre/#dd-51</link><description>The blackest and most evil painting in the world. In pursuit of its mystery, Rohan Kishibe, a manga artist with a special power, visits the Louvre in France. There, a number of horrifying events await him...</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 10:06:55 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">58d42bf23a61a2dd52463d6071d6d4637271a5faa470ccfea63fb3df11a5578f</guid></item><item><title>Harlan Coben's Shelter</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/harlan-cobens-shelter/#season-1</link><description>Follow the story of Mickey Bolitar after the death of his father leads him to start a new life in suburban New Jersey. When another new student disappears, Mickey finds himself tangled in a web of secrets. With the help of two new friends, Spoon and Ema, they reveal a dark underground that may hold the answers to decades of disappearances.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 10:06:55 -0000</pubDate><category>TV</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">b05a2cbcb3a2621aa0c444fb8100139aac7d8e0957a52c3767235205565b6a0e</guid></item><item><title>Killer Coaster</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/killer-coaster/#season-1</link><description>Summer 1998. Palavas-les-Flots. While the World Cup is in full swing, Sandrine Laplace, a bumbling contract worker who thinks she's a CIA agent, decides to investigate a mysterious accident that happened on the ghost train at the local fair. Incompetent but reckless, Sandrine infiltrates a brutal world - made up of clan wars, cotton candy and bumper cars - and will have to form an alliance with Carmen and Yvane, two showmen who are completely opposite. What if there was a murderer in the carnival?</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 10:06:55 -0000</pubDate><category>TV</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">1405e497964bd98587476308185e7213287f06d171ca834cba43542adf11d6ef</guid></item><item><title>The Wheel of Time</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/the-wheel-of-time/#season-2</link><description>Follow Moiraine, a member of the shadowy and influential all-female organization called the “Aes Sedai” as she embarks on a dangerous, world-spanning journey with five young men and women. Moiraine believes one of them might be the reincarnation of an incredibly powerful individual, whom prophecies say will either save humanity or destroy it.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 10:06:55 -0000</pubDate><category>TV</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">850a586a959d32ef8792e5f509386e0096c682ef2e3a6afd08b5ff6db6c910b3</guid></item><item><title>No One Will Save You</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/halcyon888/no-one-will-save-you/#dd-atmos</link><description>An exiled anxiety-ridden homebody must battle an alien who's found its way into her home.</description><pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2023 21:14:55 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>halcyon888</category><guid isPermaLink="false">c39765a65abcace78f625bac8876dc6346dde2626f7ff11444c51b8c75fd83df</guid></item><item><title>Gandeevadhari Arjuna</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/gandeevadhari-arjuna/#dd-51</link><description>Ex-special forces officer turned Private security bodyguard Arjun Varma, agrees to protect Central Environment Minister Adtiya Raj Bahadur while he’s in London for a Climate Change Conference at the UN. But a series of events force him to protect much more than his client.</description><pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2023 05:08:54 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">48252836f436f6c5def4f44a1e8a52754589391f5fd56273bd01cb69cfcf6b3c</guid></item><item><title>Three Days of the Condor</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/three-days-of-the-condor/#dts-hd-ma-51</link><description>A bookish CIA researcher finds all his co-workers dead, and must outwit those responsible until he figures out who he can really trust.</description><pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2023 05:06:02 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">bddfdb647246555e9e48e9f71537c50425d7c2720d8080c2fd327fcae86bddc6</guid></item><item><title>War of the Worlds</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/halcyon888/war-of-the-worlds/#dts-hd-ma-51</link><description>Ray Ferrier is a divorced dockworker and less-than-perfect father. Soon after his ex-wife and her new husband drop off his teenage son and young daughter for a rare weekend visit, a strange and powerful lightning storm touches down.</description><pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2023 01:01:30 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>halcyon888</category><guid isPermaLink="false">d636b95a05a2651a8bf803404c36d26994d3759ebc3c5d49d055624709a10d0b</guid></item><item><title>Blind</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/blind_780381/#dd-51</link><description>A brutal cat and mouse game between a blind ex-cop Gia Singh and a psychopathic serial killer, who likes to torture and kill young women.</description><pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2023 00:10:23 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">fdbfe61e11a70693aff0bc9b72ddf773bd48c1911525947b4693f3d90c2ca76e</guid></item><item><title>The Retirement Plan</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/the-retirement-plan/#dd-51</link><description>When Ashley and her young daughter Sarah get caught up in a criminal enterprise that puts their lives at risk, she turns to the only person who can help: her estranged father Matt, currently living the life of a retired beach bum in the Cayman Islands. Their reunion is fleeting as they are soon tracked down on the island by crime boss Donnie and his lieutenant Bobo. As Ashley, Sarah, and Matt become entangled in an increasingly dangerous web, Ashley quickly learns her father had a secret past that she knew nothing about and that there is more to her father than meets the eye.</description><pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2023 00:10:23 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">77d862308a2b41a6ec502197604f2b335a3a9993a98c667b5d5b56bf81840b16</guid></item><item><title>Battlestar Galactica</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/halcyon888/battlestar-galactica/#dts-hd-ma-51</link><description>After the destruction of the Twelve Colonies of Mankind, the last major fighter carrier leads a makeshift fugitive fleet in a desperate search for the legendary planet Earth. This film is adapted from a television series that aired on ABC from September 17, 1978, to August 17, 1980. The first and fifth episodes of the series were edited into this theatrical feature film. Taken together, the two episodes ran 148 minutes, without commercials, while the film runs 125 minutes.</description><pubDate>Sat, 23 Sep 2023 21:16:17 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>halcyon888</category><guid isPermaLink="false">1601ace1ad86ae952b61abedf83e14b6f883af10fd073ccb5fb2050462c454ed</guid></item><item><title>Live Free or Die Hard</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/halcyon888/live-free-or-die-hard/#dts-hd-ma-71</link><description>John McClane is back and badder than ever, and this time he's working for Homeland Security. He calls on the services of a young hacker in his bid to stop a ring of Internet terrorists intent on taking control of America's computer infrastructure.</description><pubDate>Sat, 23 Sep 2023 16:30:21 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>halcyon888</category><guid isPermaLink="false">d3f4f50039b4a6718130281005b60493e1a2541123cfc4b5c3b42ce9b88c18b1</guid></item><item><title>Fall</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/fall/#atmos</link><description>For best friends Becky and Hunter, life is all about conquering fears and pushing limits. But after they climb 2,000 feet to the top of a remote, abandoned radio tower, they find themselves stranded with no way down. Now Becky and Hunter’s expert climbing skills will be put to the ultimate test as they desperately fight to survive the elements, a lack of supplies, and vertigo-inducing heights</description><pubDate>Sat, 23 Sep 2023 09:16:12 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">17f75b70f9e44e93f6e8d0685ba3ab55d898fa7f1f054f71682d0889f5e50533</guid></item><item><title>Golmaal Again</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/golmaal-again/#dd-51</link><description>Gopal and his best friends are back again, and this time they move back to their old neighborhood in a new palatial house where they learn that it is being haunted by a ghost.</description><pubDate>Sat, 23 Sep 2023 09:16:12 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">eb77c619b7dae47cb6fcdf75ffff5255b670adb2debcef7f52926fcb998ddadb</guid></item><item><title>No One Will Save You</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/no-one-will-save-you/#dd-atmos-dd-51</link><description>A young woman who's been alienated from her community finds herself in a face-off against a host of extraterrestrial beings who threaten her future while forcing her to deal with her past.</description><pubDate>Sat, 23 Sep 2023 02:36:32 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">92b4729aa0d78d911cb2c2dd960db4daadf12da3761c5d7263f7d4f133c10aa2</guid></item><item><title>Spy Kids: Armageddon</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/spy-kids-armageddon/#dd-atmos</link><description>When the children of the world’s greatest secret agents unwittingly help a powerful game developer unleash a computer virus that gives him control of all technology, they must become spies themselves to save their parents and the world.</description><pubDate>Sat, 23 Sep 2023 01:20:34 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">b0176e08b10ae778ce15a80a9cdc0462d1d0bcb69852c9058cc8a1cad15a525e</guid></item><item><title>Accused</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/accused/#dd-51</link><description>After a revenge obsessed society incorrectly selects its next target, a young man must survive the night as the online witch-hunt arrives at his front door.</description><pubDate>Sat, 23 Sep 2023 01:00:08 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">4b9b71c25664ff9f2bbd011b6aa6d8f8a8d4377e3c5313067b6c096469e8c5c2</guid></item><item><title>The Black Book</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/the-black-book/#dd-51</link><description>After his son is wrongly accused of kidnapping, a deacon who has just lost his wife takes matters into his own hands and fights a crooked police gang to clear him.</description><pubDate>Sat, 23 Sep 2023 01:00:08 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">6fc49d4553231bb4e527d369e456bb099cf5d887017ae9fc4dbb54d2aa8ad4f6</guid></item><item><title>Cocaine Bear</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/cocaine-bear/#atmos</link><description>Inspired by a true story, an oddball group of cops, criminals, tourists and teens converge in a Georgia forest where a 500-pound black bear goes on a murderous rampage after unintentionally ingesting cocaine.</description><pubDate>Sat, 23 Sep 2023 01:00:08 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">f41a87ced7367bb61679176d35bdf7fddc6ec21aef1c861622e22bc74100845b</guid></item><item><title>Singham</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/singham/#dts-hd-ma-51-lpcm-51</link><description>An honest, small town cop is transferred to a big city that is controlled by a crime boss that he had once humiliated.</description><pubDate>Sat, 23 Sep 2023 01:00:08 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">d35668cfa6e388c1a6f58eefa56581a6ba7e1092d8f6facfb8b87ba6d352096c</guid></item><item><title>Song of the Bandits</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/song-of-the-bandits/#season-1</link><description>In the lawless land of Gando, fierce bandits will stop at nothing to fight for their precious homeland and loved ones — even if it means life or death.</description><pubDate>Sat, 23 Sep 2023 01:00:08 -0000</pubDate><category>TV</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">b3cc0f0202e4f6ff730a99fd6525d7cfec19ea1d625bd6a5a06d97a7d54031a3</guid></item><item><title>The Little Stranger</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/the-little-stranger/#dts-hd-ma-51</link><description>In a dusty post-war summer in rural Warwickshire, a doctor is called to a patient at lonely Hundreds Hall. Home to the Ayres family for over two centuries, the Georgian house is now in decline. But are the Ayreses haunted by something more sinister than a dying way of life?</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2023 19:37:23 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">d4b7cfc9cc0033c0423f0847c46001119bcc51e7b38cc176788fd77b0cabdcb2</guid></item><item><title>The Shepherd: Border Patrol</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/the-shepherd-border-patrol/#dd-51</link><description>A Texas cop battles ex-navy seals who are trying to traffic drugs from Mexico into the USA.</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2023 19:37:23 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">57876bb7fc2a382cf61797a4f907d43c13d4faa8507fab74a2c233b849fad0e5</guid></item><item><title>Cobweb</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/halcyon888/cobweb/#dd</link><description>Eight year old Peter is plagued by a mysterious, constant tapping from inside his bedroom wall—one that his parents insist is all in his imagination. As Peter's fear intensifies, he believes that his parents could be hiding a terrible, dangerous secret and questions their trustworthiness.</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2023 19:25:32 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>halcyon888</category><guid isPermaLink="false">5592c29934bd5195efcafc226f9b299cf2bd4912675c29101e9bd3da9a1d2fb3</guid></item><item><title>Cobweb</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/halcyon888/cobweb/#dts-hd-ma-51</link><description>Eight year old Peter is plagued by a mysterious, constant tapping from inside his bedroom wall—one that his parents insist is all in his imagination. As Peter's fear intensifies, he believes that his parents could be hiding a terrible, dangerous secret and questions their trustworthiness.</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2023 19:25:32 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>halcyon888</category><guid isPermaLink="false">4beedff15fa0d7fced2d29b753dee0d6a4b0ef979b82712dcbd1cb08f8575ef5</guid></item><item><title>The Continental: From the World of John Wick</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/halcyon888/the-continental-from-the-world-of-john-wick/#season-1-episode-1</link><description>Winston Scott is roped into a world of assassins and must make things right after his brother's attack on the Continental hotel.</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2023 14:36:42 -0000</pubDate><category>TV</category><category>halcyon888</category><guid isPermaLink="false">fd7ae1d5e69b58674b9f7c65ca832345a78a76504f6928b827d808f77bbcda1b</guid></item><item><title>The Wheel of Time</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/halcyon888/the-wheel-of-time/#season-2-episode-6</link><description>Follow Moiraine, a member of the shadowy and influential all-female organization called the “Aes Sedai” as she embarks on a dangerous, world-spanning journey with five young men and women. Moiraine believes one of them might be the reincarnation of an incredibly powerful individual, whom prophecies say will either save humanity or destroy it.</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2023 14:36:42 -0000</pubDate><category>TV</category><category>halcyon888</category><guid isPermaLink="false">bac05d73c5b3bbeb128825c85071e79f926a5d7a2967203ec4692836ebb398cf</guid></item><item><title>Dabangg</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/dabangg/#dts-hd-ma-51</link><description>A troubled relationship with his younger half-brother and stepfather compels Chulbul Pandey to become a corrupt but fearless cop whose life changes when he locks horns with a corrupt political leader.</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2023 07:49:26 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">8b5a2260d6a6c278173429f540bcbda151c02fd0020ee1ff3b12a5e1e6e60145</guid></item><item><title>Beaten to Death</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/halcyon888/beaten-to-death/#dd</link><description>A desperate choice leads Jack down a path that leaves him beaten and bruised as he struggles against man, nature and his own insanity. Stranded in the middle of nowhere after barely surviving a horrific assault, Jack encounters one local after another and quickly learns that a sick game of cat and mouse is about to begin. Battling the deranged country psychos and the harsh landscape, Jack must go to extreme lengths to survive.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2023 22:09:56 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>halcyon888</category><guid isPermaLink="false">39e39bfcec4e892f9123039552b0f029e28524d31b8b45e1af97afc7a80a3ea0</guid></item><item><title>Decibel</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/decibel/#dts-hd-ma-51</link><description>A former Naval officer with a dark past must face off against an insurgent with a sound sensitive bomb.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2023 21:47:07 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">8189a772d6ec80c42ac3b8c3b4df77b1ca8482789f969a29b8ad913a097db4e2</guid></item><item><title>The Lost City of Z</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/the-lost-city-of-z/#dts-hd-ma-51</link><description>A true-life drama in the 1920s, centering on British explorer Col. Percy Fawcett, who discovered evidence of a previously unknown, advanced civilization in the Amazon and disappeared whilst searching for it.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2023 21:47:07 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">ac786cd186e5a0e47bc620dd47fdf0192c9ddcf7d6a8afe11bc2550db4f698d9</guid></item><item><title>Phantom</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/phantom_715253/#dts-hd-ma-51</link><description>In 1933, when Korea was under Japanese occupation, five people in Gyeongseong are suspected to be “Phantom” spies of the anti-Japanese organization.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2023 21:47:07 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">5fd699648e18a7a078efc28495015259246e4679ce255f02d0e34aa7961640b6</guid></item><item><title>Shrek the Third</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/shrek-the-third/#dts-x</link><description>The King of Far Far Away has died and Shrek and Fiona are to become King &amp; Queen. However, Shrek wants to return to his cozy swamp and live in peace and quiet, so when he finds out there is another heir to the throne, they set off to bring him back to rule the kingdom.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2023 21:47:07 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">53811b42f529816a82f52a1c99c7ec59c00e0b83e51e857a95e5d18a1006b5a3</guid></item><item><title>The Squad: Home Run</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/the-squad-home-run/#dd-atmos</link><description>Former Antigang legend Niels Cartier, known for his muscular and unconventional methods, left the force following an intervention that went wrong and led to the death of his wife. When the gang of bank robbers responsible for her death reappears eight years later, Niels won't let anyone stand in his way to seek revenge. Even if it means forming an explosive duo with his temperamental 14-year-old daughter.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2023 21:47:07 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">e103effab33e5dd7972b87fa55af668ece18d51b0554ab62266f1c5234829060</guid></item><item><title>Beaten to Death</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/beaten-to-death/#dd-51</link><description>A desperate choice leads Jack down a path that leaves him beaten and bruised as he struggles against man, nature and his own insanity. Stranded in the middle of nowhere after barely surviving a horrific assault, Jack encounters one local after another and quickly learns that a sick game of cat and mouse is about to begin. Battling the deranged country psychos and the harsh landscape, Jack must go to extreme lengths to survive.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2023 19:46:25 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">b872d7f8919bc27dcde95adbf2acf8c4ef1ab837ad6cbc7b5751d9fa18a554a7</guid></item><item><title>D-Day</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/d-day/#truehd-51-dts-hd-ma-51</link><description>Four Indian agents spend nine years under cover to track down India's most wanted criminal.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2023 19:46:25 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">fe44c5c1638de2bdd88628d8649d9250a74bddcf1c7e083876063d7969eb4900</guid></item><item><title>Elemental</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/elemental/#dts-hd-ma-71</link><description>In a city where fire, water, land and air residents live together, a fiery young woman and a go-with-the-flow guy will discover something elemental: how much they have in common.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2023 19:46:25 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">fab5a43ebec2a352919e6c40cd122b5c58f9ba06e299329bff41c28493a40930</guid></item><item><title>Jeanne du Barry</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/jeanne-du-barry/#dts-hd-ma-51</link><description>The life of Jeanne Bécu, who was born as the illegitimate daughter of an impoverished seamstress in 1743 and went on to rise through the Court of Louis XV to become his last official mistress.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2023 19:46:25 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">e3937dca37c871a674fcccd08401410c90b1cca327675bff9888d1cbcb9b296b</guid></item><item><title>Kick-Ass 2</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/kick-ass-2/#dts-x</link><description>After Kick-Ass’ insane bravery inspires a new wave of self-made masked crusaders, he joins a patrol led by the Colonel Stars and Stripes. When these amateur superheroes are hunted down by Red Mist — reborn as The Mother Fucker — only the blade-wielding Hit-Girl can prevent their annihilation.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2023 19:46:25 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">86c4c6cbd6be8b6d8c8a7cfcc0323d07c709f2f0a8ae00aa8d070540497bbfbc</guid></item><item><title>The Last House on the Left</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/the-last-house-on-the-left/#dts-hd-ma-51</link><description>A group of teenage girls heading into the city hook up with a gang of drug-addled ne'er-do-wells and are brutally murdered. The killers find their way to the home of one of their victim's parents, where both father and mother exact a horrible revenge.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2023 19:46:25 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">90c0953a8295ef3495563ee27a7ff55e032b7c435bb222dab03fd8533985b260</guid></item><item><title>Ruby Gillman, Teenage Kraken</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/ruby-gillman-teenage-kraken/#truehd-71</link><description>Ruby Gillman, a sweet and awkward high school student, discovers she's a direct descendant of the warrior kraken queens. The kraken are sworn to protect the oceans of the world against the vain, power-hungry mermaids. Destined to inherit the throne from her commanding grandmother, Ruby must use her newfound powers to protect those she loves most.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2023 19:46:25 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">6ea919237f06c3b6f8b35e9fd365f8ff1f9129842b639856c80cfc6039a8f5c3</guid></item><item><title>The Little Mermaid</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/halcyon888/the-little-mermaid/#atmos</link><description>The youngest of King Triton’s daughters, and the most defiant, Ariel longs to find out more about the world beyond the sea, and while visiting the surface, falls for the dashing Prince Eric. With mermaids forbidden to interact with humans, Ariel makes a deal with the evil sea witch, Ursula, which gives her a chance to experience life on land, but ultimately places her life – and her father’s crown – in jeopardy.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2023 18:24:12 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>halcyon888</category><guid isPermaLink="false">dd405a0d1c4bc9165ebfc0dd368632524b0b97ef88d8febdbf1a0504404df016</guid></item><item><title>Airlift</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/airlift/#atmos-dts-ex-51</link><description>When Iraq invades Kuwait in August, 1990, a callous Indian businessman becomes the spokesperson for more than 170,000 stranded countrymen.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2023 11:02:55 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">265d89c9cfbf9c99f8450e35d94db9396c83d6731770c02fc21ff23419bdf9ef</guid></item><item><title>Armageddon</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/armageddon/#dts-hd-ma-51-dd-51</link><description>When an asteroid threatens to collide with Earth, NASA honcho Dan Truman determines the only way to stop it is to drill into its surface and detonate a nuclear bomb. This leads him to renowned driller Harry Stamper, who agrees to helm the dangerous space mission provided he can bring along his own hotshot crew. Among them is the cocksure A.J. who Harry thinks isn't good enough for his daughter, until the mission proves otherwise.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2023 11:02:55 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">b6578e6586a5443105aa7b1e32208f365792f2347c5efb732cce208112c19a0e</guid></item><item><title>Baby</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/baby/#dts-hd-ma-51</link><description>An elite counter-intelligence unit learns of a plot, masterminded by a maniacal madman. With the clock ticking, it's up to them to track the terrorists' international tentacles and prevent them from striking at the heart of India.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2023 11:02:55 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">7ac9ea141776208d8d6a1f64b3dc12751fc10f4348d64a9cea98e4e1a1a2fe29</guid></item><item><title>Gone in Sixty Seconds</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/gone-in-sixty-seconds/#dd-51</link><description>Upon learning that he has to come out of retirement to steal 50 cars in one night to save his brother Kip's life, former car thief Randall "Memphis" Raines enlists help from a few "boost happy" pals to accomplish a seemingly impossible feat. From countless car chases to relentless cops, the high-octane excitement builds as Randall swerves around more than a few roadblocks to keep Kip alive.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2023 11:02:55 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">54b662f8abdf168835beaba6039644054818caaa0446ca755712b729fab36004</guid></item><item><title>Gone in Sixty Seconds</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/gone-in-sixty-seconds/#lpcm-51</link><description>Upon learning that he has to come out of retirement to steal 50 cars in one night to save his brother Kip's life, former car thief Randall "Memphis" Raines enlists help from a few "boost happy" pals to accomplish a seemingly impossible feat. From countless car chases to relentless cops, the high-octane excitement builds as Randall swerves around more than a few roadblocks to keep Kip alive.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2023 11:02:55 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">78a4944fcd492af8ee756f3a58917d9c0b290d6e32fcbfb0cb617eca33c22d3e</guid></item><item><title>Jai Ho</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/jai-ho/#dts-hd-ma-71</link><description>An upright ex-army man, Jai fights a solitary war against corruption and injustice. With a simple mantra to pay forward, he starts off by helping one person and forms an ever growing circle of people helping each other.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2023 11:02:55 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">e33a1b0080937fc59e1f433561edb4706468c50c549e4aacbd872da328fb586d</guid></item><item><title>Race</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/race/#dts-hd-ma-51</link><description>The plot thickens around two horse-racing competitors when three beautiful women come into their lives and a murder is committed.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2023 11:02:55 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">339b80d84d1607dcbacdcb71b6f9950c398ed41fc0b3982ad5b372f0055c3066</guid></item><item><title>Jaane Jaan</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/jaane-jaan/#dd-atmos</link><description>When a single mother becomes ensnared in a deadly crime, her neighbor — a gifted math teacher — comes to her aid and a tenacious cop digs into the case.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2023 11:02:55 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">8d9fcb2f7ac8349c4ff79634a63a36f565c2531741e9219254559f5cb9ddeb13</guid></item><item><title>Wazir</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/wazir/#atmos-dd-ex-61</link><description>'Wazir' is a tale of two unlikely friends, a wheelchair-bound chess grandmaster and a brave ATS officer. Brought together by grief and a strange twist of fate, the two men decide to help each other win the biggest games of their lives. But there's a mysterious, dangerous opponent lurking in the shadows, who is all set to checkmate them.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2023 11:02:55 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">3f6b35558beb52f147affcbacb57eb78c13ad437c24072365b74f17a09bded53</guid></item><item><title>Club Dread</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/club-dread/#dd-51</link><description>When a serial killer interrupts the fun at the swanky Coconut Pete's Coconut Beach Resort -- a hedonistic island paradise for swingers --- it's up to the club's staff to stop the violence ... or at least hide it!</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 19:33:23 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">4c563320c1615a60fad9fa0db7fc603ec997cdaed10705516d801dd65144c0cd</guid></item><item><title>Con Air</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/con-air/#lpcm-51-dd-51-dd-51</link><description>Newly-paroled former US Army ranger Cameron Poe is headed back to his wife, but must fly home aboard a prison transport flight dubbed "Jailbird" taking the “worst of the worst” prisoners, a group described as “pure predators”, to a new super-prison. Poe faces impossible odds when the transport plane is skyjacked mid-flight by the most vicious criminals in the country led by the mastermind — genius serial killer Cyrus "The Virus" Grissom, and backed by black militant Diamond Dog and psychopath Billy Bedlam.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 19:33:23 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">967bd6159d26879f433d8fc4feedfea2214a3d326719b4f8d2a7ae82a07715ed</guid></item><item><title>Déjà Vu</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/deja-vu/#lpcm-51-dd-51</link><description>Called in to recover evidence in the aftermath of a horrific explosion on a New Orleans ferry, Federal agent Doug Carlin gets pulled away from the scene and taken to a top-secret government lab that uses a time-shifting surveillance device to help prevent crime.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 19:33:23 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">3b2df0a8d7a83140cd922b3fccda3a43109ed190db1de57622bfbe6380dccce8</guid></item><item><title>The Day After Tomorrow</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/the-day-after-tomorrow/#dts-hd-ma-51-dd-51</link><description>After years of increases in the greenhouse effect,  havoc is wreaked globally in the form of catastrophic hurricanes, tornadoes, tidal waves, floods and the beginning of a new Ice Age. Paleoclimatologist, Jack Hall tries to warn the world while also shepherding to safety his son, trapped in New York after the city is overwhelmed by the start of the new big freeze.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 19:33:23 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">0dc1e08ea344d2e3bdc07caba04c3953923d53bd1d0ca76650d4f1822db49ae5</guid></item><item><title>Enemy of the State</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/enemy-of-the-state/#lpcm-51-dd-51</link><description>A hotshot Washington criminal lawyer becomes the target of a rogue security executive videotaped in the act of murdering a congressman when the incriminating tape is surreptitiously slipped into his shopping bag by the videographer, who is fleeing the executive's assassins.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 19:33:23 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">98396254f2eebae65acf3b6f59c2d881219243f790a5d9b39d4534f0cf100a10</guid></item><item><title>Ghost Rider</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/ghost-rider/#dd-51</link><description>In order to save his dying father, young stunt cyclist Johnny Blaze sells his soul to Mephistopheles and sadly parts from the pure-hearted Roxanne Simpson, the love of his life. Years later, Johnny's path crosses again with Roxanne, now a go-getting reporter, and also with Mephistopheles, who offers to release Johnny's soul if Johnny becomes the fabled, fiery 'Ghost Rider'.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 19:33:23 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">928a8d4c6ec558e687b1f09e75624bdf2c1239199adeb8c1fba5a052a5453f77</guid></item><item><title>Pathfinder</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/pathfinder/#dd-51</link><description>A Viking boy is left behind after his clan battles a Native American tribe. Raised within the tribe, he ultimately becomes their savior in a fight against the Norsemen.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 19:33:23 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">cbb9302296548f539b1175ae028b913ba48dc49924d5f1056bb1e169629af166</guid></item><item><title>Ready or Not</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/ready-or-not/#dts-hd-ma-51-dd-51</link><description>A bride's wedding night takes a sinister turn when her eccentric new in-laws force her to take part in a terrifying game.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 19:33:23 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">880edffb74dc2b1d034142d2c9ff508e3dea41a5d369d76b00cda9dc64a0bb07</guid></item><item><title>The Rock</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/the-rock/#lpcm-51-dd-51</link><description>FBI chemical warfare expert Stanley Goodspeed is sent on an urgent mission with a former British spy, John Patrick Mason, to stop Gen. Francis X. Hummel from launching chemical weapons on Alcatraz Island into San Francisco. Gen. Hummel demands $100 million in war reparations to be paid to the families of slain servicemen who died on covert operations. After their SEAL team is wiped out, Stanley and John deal with the soldiers on their own.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 19:33:23 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">78d8c92d68af67d8a5a562dd131bd33798f16c66d5cf7bb03d55630f413aac5a</guid></item><item><title>Spotlight</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/spotlight/#dts-hd-ma-51</link><description>The true story of how the Boston Globe uncovered the massive scandal of child molestation and cover-up within the local Catholic Archdiocese, shaking the entire Catholic Church to its core.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 19:33:23 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">43ca084929f027d72fd34ea16e040e7dca20fd7bcaea3c579c22a77bfc193c61</guid></item><item><title>The Transporter</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/the-transporter/#dd-51</link><description>Former Special Forces officer, Frank Martin will deliver anything to anyone for the right price, and his no-questions-asked policy puts him in high demand. But when he realizes his latest cargo is alive, it sets in motion a dangerous chain of events. The bound and gagged Lai is being smuggled to France by a shady American businessman, and Frank works to save her as his own illegal activities are uncovered by a French detective.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 19:33:23 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">e1372642f37de668b0b274b69818e87a1b570a41a861b2f1fce7d00141df7503</guid></item><item><title>My Brilliant Friend</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/my-brilliant-friend/#season-1</link><description>When the most important friend in her life seems to have disappeared without a trace, Elena Greco, a now-elderly woman immersed in a house full of books, turns on her computer and starts writing the story of their friendship.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 19:33:23 -0000</pubDate><category>TV</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">c11e29140dfe74070c465e89d1d59e76416de583233ca5a6231ecab1705da4a8</guid></item><item><title>The Mandalorian</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/the-mandalorian/#season-1</link><description>After the fall of the Galactic Empire, lawlessness has spread throughout the galaxy. A lone gunfighter makes his way through the outer reaches, earning his keep as a bounty hunter.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 19:33:23 -0000</pubDate><category>TV</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">897fcd4e1450a25ecbe736ca01c3631f7f52b174003300becc47f3340cd2c0ae</guid></item><item><title>The Mandalorian</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/the-mandalorian/#season-2</link><description>After the fall of the Galactic Empire, lawlessness has spread throughout the galaxy. A lone gunfighter makes his way through the outer reaches, earning his keep as a bounty hunter.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 19:33:23 -0000</pubDate><category>TV</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">f3dfe8435a503e5559696c438774d851a8a2b902dab4ea60a0908de64f6150bc</guid></item><item><title>Ahsoka</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/halcyon888/ahsoka/#season-1-episode-6</link><description>Former Jedi Knight Ahsoka Tano investigates an emerging threat to a vulnerable galaxy.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 18:25:55 -0000</pubDate><category>TV</category><category>halcyon888</category><guid isPermaLink="false">a6108e79e22d046ef212da9e5b0714262a093c907a431371e2098c4728181efb</guid></item><item><title>Blood Money</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/blood-money_105379/#dd-51</link><description>In South Africa, a young man living with his wife becomes embroiled in an illegal diamond business and with time finds his life changing.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 08:22:18 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">c3be65e8d75e9c05e71c31dd6365273690d83b5dcebc7ab5e16e8d91db284dc8</guid></item><item><title>Kaminey</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/kaminey/#dd-51</link><description>Two brothers, as different as chalk and cheese, find their lives intertwined when one puts himself in danger via a `get rich quick' scheme and the other finds there is a price on his head.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 08:22:18 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">de8bb6021a807f695ffc7fba18b7af334232c242f4d0d43c2589c49df84977b8</guid></item><item><title>Main Hoon Na</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/main-hoon-na/#dd-51</link><description>An army major goes undercover as a college student. His mission is both professional and personal: to protect his general's daughter from a radical militant, and to find his estranged half-brother.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2023 21:25:26 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">d3023de3873ee0e7782fbc9aa7060336ef617734625d0c5f9ecaf0d7d92030a4</guid></item><item><title>Bird Box Barcelona</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/bird-box-barcelona/#dd-atmos</link><description>After a mysterious force decimates the world’s population, Sebastian must navigate his own survival journey through the desolate streets of Barcelona. As he forms uneasy alliances with other survivors and they try to escape the city, an unexpected and even more sinister threat grows.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2023 18:19:40 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">5c0bbd0798b4ce97bcd9bd859b197737aafecc34af6c3ac61f1ef0fe2fda887d</guid></item><item><title>Mister Organ</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/mister-organ/#dts-hd-ma-51</link><description>Following reports of fraudulent car clamping in Auckland, journalist and filmmaker David Farrier opens an investigation that pushes him to the limits of his sanity in this incredible true story of psychological warfare.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2023 18:19:40 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">d392b82e7b0bb2c60e7e4890a53c575f471819468d219e7d8551ce496943c08a</guid></item><item><title>Nandor Fodor and the Talking Mongoose</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/nandor-fodor-and-the-talking-mongoose/#dd-51</link><description>In 1935, Hungarian-American para-psychologist Nandor Fodor began his investigation of a strange occurrence on the Isle of Man. An average British family, the Irvings, claimed to have been contacted by a mysterious entity at their farm. A talking mongoose. Named Gef (Pronounced "Jeff".)</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2023 18:19:40 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">7bef105b9972e8069e7876687037a4409b192582a41fd1cab27fd36b1fb1f7f2</guid></item><item><title>Operation Mincemeat</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/operation-mincemeat/#dts-hd-ma-51</link><description>In 1943, two British intelligence officers concoct Operation Mincemeat, wherein their plan to drop a corpse with false papers off the coast of Spain would fool Nazi spies into believing the Allied forces were planning to attack by way of Greece rather than Sicily.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2023 18:19:40 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">5dc81e162db0721d1c76d50813123760c4eeeca7f23a092c45305df7e3f684f3</guid></item><item><title>Til Death Do Us Part</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/til-death-do-us-part/#dd-51</link><description>After bailing on her wedding, a former bride-to-be must fight off her ex-groom and seven angry killer groomsmen in order to survive the night.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2023 18:19:40 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">966e42b089a35e7c5e7665b01422d1c383dcfce14c5760708e0f41b1080e444d</guid></item><item><title>Ek Tha Tiger</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/ek-tha-tiger/#truehd-71-dts-hd-ma-51</link><description>An Indian agent is sent to observe the actions of a scientist but the mission becomes complicated when he falls in love with the scientist's Pakistani caretaker.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2023 10:57:39 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">3682c7a48061d7ee94f7f199dfc3f1ac0757d5caa72cf72d32d4385ac545354a</guid></item><item><title>Singham Returns</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/singham-returns/#dts-hd-ma-51</link><description>Singham Returns is an Indian action film directed by Rohit Shetty and produced by Reliance Entertainment. The sequel to the 2011 film Singham, actor Ajay Devgn reprises his role from the previous film, as well as co-producing the project, while Kareena Kapoor Khan plays the female lead.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2023 10:57:39 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">3eebd635d5988dad5e40e36039c0853114a46cd8dc22122e7451a4ad325b4ec9</guid></item><item><title>Tiger Zinda Hai</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/tiger-zinda-hai/#atmos</link><description>When a group of Indian and Pakistani nurses are held hostage in Iraq by a terrorist organization, a secret agent is drawn out of hiding to rescue them.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2023 10:57:39 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">e79d67016c14379f7bc3d733b70e4e7fad5f1b344fcb7ffbb540901593ba37e9</guid></item><item><title>Blue Beetle</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/t1g8rsfan/blue-beetle/#dd-atmos</link><description>Recent college grad Jaime Reyes returns home full of aspirations for his future, only to find that home is not quite as he left it. As he searches to find his purpose in the world, fate intervenes when Jaime unexpectedly finds himself in possession of an ancient relic of alien biotechnology: the Scarab.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2023 03:56:54 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>t1g8rsfan</category><guid isPermaLink="false">e2213a0d1d68dbd45dfa76941a7811cee2e5d3ec279c9786af08b8c2bfe2506b</guid></item><item><title>The Little Mermaid</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/t1g8rsfan/the-little-mermaid/#atmos-dd-atmos</link><description>The youngest of King Triton’s daughters, and the most defiant, Ariel longs to find out more about the world beyond the sea, and while visiting the surface, falls for the dashing Prince Eric. With mermaids forbidden to interact with humans, Ariel makes a deal with the evil sea witch, Ursula, which gives her a chance to experience life on land, but ultimately places her life – and her father’s crown – in jeopardy.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2023 03:56:54 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>t1g8rsfan</category><guid isPermaLink="false">48526e9169b7e22dde34be5d91242ae329082e4eaa9c9cbfcef851f8317f29d5</guid></item><item><title>Cobweb</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/cobweb/#dts-hd-ma-51-dd-51</link><description>Eight year old Peter is plagued by a mysterious, constant tapping from inside his bedroom wall—one that his parents insist is all in his imagination. As Peter's fear intensifies, he believes that his parents could be hiding a terrible, dangerous secret and questions their trustworthiness.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2023 03:31:24 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">f1038c35daa5820daed95a7db9c29a6a89b7835744af720fff30d57b9cfebfb9</guid></item><item><title>That Demon Within</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/that-demon-within/#dd-51</link><description>By a strange twist of fate, dutiful Hong Kong policeman Dan saves the life of the leader of a violent gang of armed robbers.  When they commit another crime, Dan is determined to put an end to their activities.  He works with the leader, whom the gang had betrayed, to engineer a plan to wreak havoc within the gang and let the gangsters kill one another.  But it becomes increasingly obvious to Dan and to his colleagues that Dan is suffering from a severe mental disorder, and Dan finds that instead of upholding the law as a righteous police officer, he has now become a fugitive wanted for murder.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2023 22:42:47 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">7bcc6b3ebd7bc84b2bb09c4d5ac20b997b3a497d40e9081c24d9e20757753ead</guid></item><item><title>Guy Ritchie's The Covenant</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/guy-ritchies-the-covenant/#atmos-dd-atmos</link><description>During the war in Afghanistan, a local interpreter risks his own life to carry an injured sergeant across miles of grueling terrain.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2023 19:15:56 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">31e2a65c88a2f6525d493db0d91c63a25510a3fdbcd377204a10128d9010ce1c</guid></item><item><title>Born to Fly</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/born-to-fly/#truehd-51</link><description>A talented trainee pilot is given the opportunity to virtually test the latest fighter jet, which pushes him to his limits.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2023 18:45:05 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">2e4b4af1329995b38bd62f6fb328d3b52df9f9b009610ccd7437ef188eab9df7</guid></item><item><title>Blue Beetle</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/blue-beetle/#dd-atmos</link><description>Recent college grad Jaime Reyes returns home full of aspirations for his future, only to find that home is not quite as he left it. As he searches to find his purpose in the world, fate intervenes when Jaime unexpectedly finds himself in possession of an ancient relic of alien biotechnology: the Scarab.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2023 18:24:18 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">c295360e3d8dc37f30bf9647c590c1576fb7f22416f3568e275f5a98c06fa085</guid></item><item><title>The Little Mermaid</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/the-little-mermaid/#atmos-dd-atmos-dts-hd-ma-71</link><description>The youngest of King Triton’s daughters, and the most defiant, Ariel longs to find out more about the world beyond the sea, and while visiting the surface, falls for the dashing Prince Eric. With mermaids forbidden to interact with humans, Ariel makes a deal with the evil sea witch, Ursula, which gives her a chance to experience life on land, but ultimately places her life – and her father’s crown – in jeopardy.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2023 18:24:18 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">e519d373680d4acd082ac5d3f1fdc1141050acd17ee8cf8a802663f02c74b8b9</guid></item><item><title>Blue Beetle</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/halcyon888/blue-beetle/#dd-atmos</link><description>Recent college grad Jaime Reyes returns home full of aspirations for his future, only to find that home is not quite as he left it. As he searches to find his purpose in the world, fate intervenes when Jaime unexpectedly finds himself in possession of an ancient relic of alien biotechnology: the Scarab.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2023 17:25:11 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>halcyon888</category><guid isPermaLink="false">8d0f92c6aa4303f532920850807819e00040d389f033ebf5fdff60d398fd2ce5</guid></item><item><title>The Legend of Zorro</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/the-legend-of-zorro/#atmos</link><description>Having spent the last 10 years fighting injustice and cruelty, Alejandro de la Vega is now facing his greatest challenge: his loving wife Elena has thrown him out of the house!  Elena has filed for divorce and found comfort in the arms of Count Armand, a dashing French aristocrat.  But Alejandro knows something she doesn't: Armand is the evil mastermind behind a terrorist plot to destroy the United States.  And so, with his marriage and the county's future at stake, it's up to Zorro to save two unions before it's too late.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2023 09:50:29 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">7c66d7fb1ff204634852ab789c42478209510599fbdf502e4ff7dd8422480f47</guid></item><item><title>Attack</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/attack/#dd-51</link><description>With the Parliament under siege, India’s first super soldier Arjun Shergill is tasked to get hold of the terrorists in the nick of time, save the Prime Minister from their clutches and stop a dirty bomb from exploding and destroying Delhi. Will Arjun succeed in his mission?</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2023 09:42:57 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">603b5a9a7745e0c856d486d8cdc38a1b72f760f16d40e5765ba19db8713d9964</guid></item><item><title>Come Back Home</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/come-back-home/#dd-51</link><description>A young boy, Lele, goes missing in the Changbai mountains after an argument with this father. Approaching the vital 48 hour mark and with no sign of Lele, his father takes it upon himself to brave an upcoming avalanche to save his son</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2023 09:42:57 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">6d735cded5c53b4e4263d89771b2ac0a080786be8917327329dc5d23f9444a8e</guid></item><item><title>Once Upon a Time in Hong Kong</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/once-upon-a-time-in-hong-kong/#aac-51</link><description>The story tells the story of a collusion between Hong Kong police and criminals in 1973, under the instigation of the British, they embezzled huge profits and poisoned the citizens. The Governor of Hong Kong established the Independent Commission Against Corruption</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2023 09:42:57 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">c83111564344a7c9594bacb5d589699c152b5fdb33810bf0155aa7c274af148d</guid></item><item><title>Quasi</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/quasi/#dd-51</link><description>A hapless hunchback who only yearns for love, finds himself in the middle of a murderous feud between the Pope and the King of France when each orders the hunchback to kill the other.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2023 09:42:57 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">f72c6a483f0adafcb4911293ecaf9aafbcbaa410b1c9ffb5bbabdc7d9c7fa775</guid></item><item><title>Radhe</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/radhe/#dd-51</link><description>As Mumbai’s youth are falling prey to rampant drug abuse, suspended cop Radhe is recalled for a clean-up mission. But Radhe is up against a dangerous new outlaw Rana, who will stop at nothing to rule the city.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2023 09:42:57 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">ad4b0004a834172831ffb98ce41ccf50c14ab4de77a1f00ef339214849e1e825</guid></item><item><title>Radhe</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/radhe/#dts-ex-51</link><description>As Mumbai’s youth are falling prey to rampant drug abuse, suspended cop Radhe is recalled for a clean-up mission. But Radhe is up against a dangerous new outlaw Rana, who will stop at nothing to rule the city.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2023 09:42:57 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">236a7932a2d7482d1a6d104027e7e8edc4cbf0e9272966e459905914481c180f</guid></item><item><title>The Roundup</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/the-roundup/#dts-hd-ma-51-dd-51</link><description>The ‘Beast Cop’ Ma Seok-do heads to a foreign country to extradite a suspect, but soon after his arrival, he discovers additional murder cases and hears about a vicious killer who has been committing crimes against tourists for several years.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2023 09:42:57 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">7c82b8d29f3c63584a736de9676899a2f1d17ae89f8c3c6ae613a5545651a9cf</guid></item><item><title>Simmba</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/simmba/#dts-hd-ma-51</link><description>A corrupt police officer enjoys all the perks of being an immoral and unethical police officer until an event which transforms his life completely and forces him to choose the righteous path.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2023 09:42:57 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">c3c37e09ca270a25c2a5b1b013d8324ef27bf0ea94b6ed6ce836df1754076fb9</guid></item><item><title>The Lost City of Z</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/t1g8rsfan/the-lost-city-of-z/#dts-hd-ma-51</link><description>A true-life drama in the 1920s, centering on British explorer Col. Percy Fawcett, who discovered evidence of a previously unknown, advanced civilization in the Amazon and disappeared whilst searching for it.</description><pubDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2023 17:34:59 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>t1g8rsfan</category><guid isPermaLink="false">508ddbb2cf506c6774634d894a66353d204c6cacdf9abd4ea988888f04e3ad2c</guid></item><item><title>Boogie Nights</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/boogie-nights/#dd-51</link><description>A fantasy film in which the world is coming to an end due to North Korea's sudden announcement of a nuclear explosion, and an ordinary office worker meets five women while planning to live his last day without regret, and finds his life as he is caught up in an unexpected extreme situation.</description><pubDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2023 10:22:58 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">217458fad6df9ceec084e267f9c383a77273992c99642fcbdb92419d6379015a</guid></item><item><title>Die Hard</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/die-hard/#dts-hd-ma-51</link><description>NYPD cop John McClane's plan to reconcile with his estranged wife is thrown for a serious loop when, minutes after he arrives at her office, the entire building is overtaken by a group of terrorists. With little help from the LAPD, wisecracking McClane sets out to single-handedly rescue the hostages and bring the bad guys down.</description><pubDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2023 10:22:58 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">1b6ec2909283d4f66b5929ac7ef52a3bfa1fa0ff0c9ca459e7885bf9f6f1ab1c</guid></item><item><title>Die Hard 2</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/die-hard-2/#dts-hd-ma-51</link><description>Off-duty cop John McClane is gripped with a feeling of déjà vu when, on a snowy Christmas Eve in the nation’s capital, terrorists seize a major international airport, holding thousands of holiday travelers hostage. Renegade military commandos led by a murderous rogue officer plot to rescue a drug lord from justice and are prepared for every contingency except one: McClane’s smart-mouthed heroics.</description><pubDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2023 10:22:58 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">c9e42624e3a4ae3c43d06ef3c5491d31bd162d71255163f976c4560dbdc0db21</guid></item><item><title>Die Hard: With a Vengeance</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/die-hard-with-a-vengeance/#dts-hd-ma-51</link><description>New York detective John McClane is back and kicking bad-guy butt in the third installment of this action-packed series, which finds him teaming with civilian Zeus Carver to prevent the loss of innocent lives. McClane thought he'd seen it all, until a genius named Simon engages McClane, his new "partner" -- and his beloved city -- in a deadly game that demands their concentration.</description><pubDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2023 10:22:58 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">4e2c2cb531ca3db925822ac5f9a8e388155d6159e651de3aa0c6fbd1bedef759</guid></item><item><title>El Conde</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/el-conde/#dd-atmos</link><description>Augusto Pinochet is a vampire ready to die, but the vultures around him won’t let him go without one last bite.</description><pubDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2023 10:22:58 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">ee96a1e1a5a06fdd70018852bc26a9f9c3c5f2645287089450936d3ca72d9dc8</guid></item><item><title>A Good Day to Die Hard</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/a-good-day-to-die-hard/#dts-hd-ma-71</link><description>Iconoclastic, take-no-prisoners cop John McClane, finds himself for the first time on foreign soil after traveling to Moscow to help his wayward son Jack - unaware that Jack is really a highly-trained CIA operative out to stop a nuclear weapons heist. With the Russian underworld in pursuit, and battling a countdown to war, the two McClanes discover that their opposing methods make them unstoppable heroes.</description><pubDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2023 10:22:58 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">cc9e176bb0ea542c3d325b4a6f3667adcbc0ffae6d5c99b3980a2177db8a1927</guid></item><item><title>A Good Day to Die Hard</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/a-good-day-to-die-hard/#dts-hd-ma-71</link><description>Iconoclastic, take-no-prisoners cop John McClane, finds himself for the first time on foreign soil after traveling to Moscow to help his wayward son Jack - unaware that Jack is really a highly-trained CIA operative out to stop a nuclear weapons heist. With the Russian underworld in pursuit, and battling a countdown to war, the two McClanes discover that their opposing methods make them unstoppable heroes.</description><pubDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2023 10:22:58 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">946e2ae6a0632452bcfededeb5c97bcd0af0f012cb830e66e124bec42560dee4</guid></item><item><title>The Ghost Station</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/the-ghost-station/#dd-51</link><description>Reporter Na-yeong and her partner investigate a series of mysterious deaths and a perplexing case where her source was allegedly already dead at the time of their interview. Together they end up confronting a terrifying truth.</description><pubDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2023 10:22:58 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">b35be3da5bfd5df19d1f85717b2ebe9cfc10fef96a2bb3c40511ef80164e4072</guid></item><item><title>Live Free or Die Hard</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/live-free-or-die-hard/#dts-hd-ma-51</link><description>John McClane is back and badder than ever, and this time he's working for Homeland Security. He calls on the services of a young hacker in his bid to stop a ring of Internet terrorists intent on taking control of America's computer infrastructure.</description><pubDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2023 10:22:58 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">4cd9ed575d351024496c77c999e9f4eab88761f4d4139a9e2ebee09411d8338d</guid></item><item><title>Live Free or Die Hard</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/live-free-or-die-hard/#dts-hd-ma-51</link><description>John McClane is back and badder than ever, and this time he's working for Homeland Security. He calls on the services of a young hacker in his bid to stop a ring of Internet terrorists intent on taking control of America's computer infrastructure.</description><pubDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2023 10:22:58 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">8860d89997d3e3761209fc3c53afbaa1d6ac67ee941fe856ff4f23228a03a830</guid></item><item><title>The Recon</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/the-recon/#dd-51</link><description>An education officer who was dispatched died after a gunshot went off in the dead of night. At the same time, deserters flee to the DMZ in the access control zone, and the 3rd platoon is urgently deployed to the DMZ search operation. There, the crew sees an unidentified soldier, not a deserter or a search crew.</description><pubDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2023 10:22:58 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">d609dfa6e979fe332c60eb4254e871c7e53413fd6006b83ea27cc7840d099a4d</guid></item><item><title>Zero Tolerance</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/zero-tolerance/#dts-hd-ma-51-dd-51</link><description>Johnny and Peter, former paramilitary operatives, search Bangkok - leaving carnage in their wake - to find the men who killed Johnny's daughter, Angel.</description><pubDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2023 10:22:58 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">de40f3b85786a7342b9ddcc8ce8151007579d6ddaa532aa40b44e3ac90ad2313</guid></item></channel></rss>