<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title>BEQCatalogue</title><description>A RSS feed containing all BEQs created in the last 2 weeks</description><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/</link><language>en-gb</language><pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 09:20:15 -0000</pubDate><atom:link href="https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/rss.xml" ref="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item><title>Brawl in Cell Block 99</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/brawl-in-cell-block-99/#dts-hd-ma-51-dd-51</link><description>After working as a drug courier and getting into a brutal shootout with police, a former boxer finds himself at the mercy of his enemies as they force him to instigate violent acts that turn the prison he resides in into a battleground.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 09:17:00 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">cb2dddf485f81210a34e933d260e9c612e6d8d1d913d0bce3c41dc29032376b3</guid></item><item><title>The Captain</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/the-captain/#dd-51</link><description>Germany, 1945. Soldier Willi Herold, a deserter of the German army, stumbles into a uniform of Nazi captain abandoned during the last and desperate weeks of the Third Reich. Newly emboldened by the allure of a suit that he has stolen only to stay warm, Willi discovers that many Germans will follow the leader, whoever he is.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 09:17:00 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">60b8b2e991a3748bce1da349e03a6c9b48ee3b9398def6f3ca92059bd7c1389c</guid></item><item><title>Vengeance: A Love Story</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/vengeance-a-love-story/#dts-hd-ma-51-dd-51</link><description>When a new friend is brutally assaulted, Detective John Droomor is put by chance in charge of the investigation. Although the evidence against the perpetrators seems overwhelming, there is nothing definitive in the case that guarantees justice is served, even more so if some people are willing to twist and betray it.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 09:17:00 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">c511c9f3bdece9bf224e94f356989e1aa9ff901ccd35151cc4aa99d0a4eebf7b</guid></item><item><title>Witchville</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/witchville/#dd-51</link><description>When Prince Malachy returns to his father’s kingdom after the Crusades his first impression is that a bad harvest is the reason that the villagers are sick and hungry. But all is not as it seems and a stranger to the village, warns the new king that a dark force is the cause of their ills.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 09:17:00 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">4f33dc8132c44aee8097a907af92d5fbc61ff3e9479bee4f42707690b9d5bedd</guid></item><item><title>Bbuddah Hoga Terra Baap</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/bbuddah-hoga-terra-baap/#dd-51</link><description>After a series of bomb blasts in Mumbai, ACP Karan Malhotra announces that he will bring in the culprits responsible within a very short period of time as well attempts to convince his college sweetheart, Tanya P. Nath, to marry him. He then sets about interrogating several suspects so much so that an underworld gangster, Kabir, is compelled to hire an assassin to do away with him. The potential killer, Viju, is an uptight older ex-convict as well as a former gangster, who now runs a pub in Paris, and is willing to kill Karan. As he sets about this gruesome task, he comes across an old flame, Kamini, as well as his estranged wife, Sita - and it is these encounters that may well be the turning point in this life that may convince him to leave the bombs and Bandooks behind and spend the rest of his life praying and watching the Bhakti Channel.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 11:10:16 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">0fdbf1f9eb477d4ef06f343b4dbd87b300758e2df7be1da9901ece607cd4dcdd</guid></item><item><title>Confidential Assignment 2: International</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/confidential-assignment-2-international/#dts-hd-ma-51</link><description>Follows Rim Chul Ryung heading back to South Korea in pursuit of a brutal and secret criminal organization. He teams up again with Kang Jin Tae, who volunteers to work with the North Korean in order to get back on the investigation team after a mistake landed him in the cyber crime department.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 11:10:16 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">6f446a36165fe070dd061004d14b1ec31f4f37176768f18be0f84d206c5068a1</guid></item><item><title>Flashover</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/flashover/#dts-hd-ma-71</link><description>A large blast hits the gas pipeline in the industrial park due to a sudden earthquake, which triggers massive explosions and engulfs the neighboring area in flames. Facing the escalating fire danger, the Fire and Rescue Force quickly reaches the hazardous zone to hold the fire and cut a firebreak, in the meantime, many survivors are pulled out of the rubble.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 11:10:16 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">372a7443e28640e1eebe1ec9819a7951cfd1e5812a6b311ca055e199ec284828</guid></item><item><title>Gupt: The Hidden Truth</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/gupt-the-hidden-truth/#lpcm-51-dd-51</link><description>When Governor Jaisingh Sinha is murdered, the needle of suspicion points towards his estranged son Sahil who has been fighting with his father over the girl he had chosen for him to marry. Sahil is in love with Isha but the governor wanted him to marry Sheetal. Now Sahil must prove his innocence and find out who the killer is.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 11:10:16 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">7a9d2234a7aaa8d379715bbea7ee4f90a13b582e36e1314e9a7da89151360a37</guid></item><item><title>Kurbaan</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/kurbaan/#dts-hd-ma-51</link><description>When a handsome young Indian couple (Saif Ali Khan and Kareena Kapoor) moves into the suburbs to claim their stake in the American dream, they are shocked to discover that they've become enmeshed in a secretive terrorist plot. But as tensions escalate, the bride begins to wonder if her husband has told her everything he knows.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 11:10:16 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">d35a1a621dadf9fbcc77767a5e155258f0f5216e922fba7d743572cd6060bc6a</guid></item><item><title>Malang</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/malang/#dd-51</link><description>Advait visits Goa where he meets Sara, a free-spirited girl who lives life unshackled. Opposites attract and all goes well until life turns upside down. Years later, Advait is on a killing spree with cops Aghase and Michael in his way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 11:10:16 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">b175b06039ae1434f5e7e5b6cf290289480e03885909cd1e5f67f2d9a9391c03</guid></item><item><title>Meter</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/meter/#dd-51</link><description>Arjun Kalyan, son of Raghunath, a police constable, ends up becoming a Sub Inspector despite his disinterest in the department. The chain of events that evolve after assuming charge brings him into a face-to-face conflict with home minister Byre Reddy, a crony and criminal politician.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 11:10:16 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">abbca9b90ef958f38ea01922d8992ece0692c4e063a7311e0216e45b448dc08a</guid></item><item><title>Once Upon a Time in Mumbaai</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/once-upon-a-time-in-mumbaai/#dts-hd-ma-51</link><description>A tale of two gangsters from the eras of past and present, whose lives enter parallel paths as they struggle to survive within Bombay's criminal underworld.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 11:10:16 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">78caa0780b57945c974895e7af34aa7888df9ac7906b468a321eb9299e037875</guid></item><item><title>Rowdy Rathore</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/rowdy-rathore/#dts-hd-ma-51</link><description>A small-time thug comes across a young girl who claims him to be her father, following which he realizes he has a lookalike who's being hunted by goons.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 11:10:16 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">2b2e2b67572139473475024fb8ddc810b0dea887c11e1b7a6c2365b052148ade</guid></item><item><title>Shootout at Lokhandwala</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/shootout-at-lokhandwala/#dts-hd-ma-51</link><description>On a calm summer day in 1991, in the bustling Lokhandwala Complex, five criminals including Maya and Dilip were counting 70 lakhs in flat no. 32 B, when 286 policemen, headed by ACP Khan, took strategic positions around their building. A gunfire ensued and the entire nation witnessed the most talked about daylight encounter lasting 6 hours that transformed suburban Mumbai into a war zone.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 11:10:16 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">77dd7d018212c3ea477299a46cdb8e26cc8184d67d666ee409c869413f86f9f5</guid></item><item><title>Strange World</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/strange-world/#dd-atmos-dd-51</link><description>A journey deep into an uncharted and treacherous land, where fantastical creatures await the legendary Clades—a family of explorers whose differences threaten to topple their latest, and by far most crucial, mission.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 11:10:16 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">69b5b4f3639cb49bfc4af60aea6637c574d6f47fefdc6f168c3e4f840af59383</guid></item><item><title>Mary and The Witch's Flower</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/t1g8rsfan/mary-and-the-witchs-flower/#dts-hd-ma-51</link><description>Mary Smith, a young girl who lives with her great-aunt in the countryside, follows a mysterious cat into the nearby forest where she finds a strange flower and an old broom, none of which is as ordinary as it seems.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 00:45:59 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>t1g8rsfan</category><guid isPermaLink="false">f47d6bfeaa79405a1ae3f65962eb6da373900ad3c3f5c09715ef93157b35608a</guid></item><item><title>Barbie</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/t1g8rsfan/barbie/#atmos</link><description>Barbie and Ken are having the time of their lives in the colorful and seemingly perfect world of Barbie Land. However, when they get a chance to go to the real world, they soon discover the joys and perils of living among humans.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 00:04:18 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>t1g8rsfan</category><guid isPermaLink="false">6aa5f7a5cbfd02a284fadec3efd32cf91408150b9451c935338940fc79f72b83</guid></item><item><title>I Know What You Did Last Summer</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/t1g8rsfan/i-know-what-you-did-last-summer/#atmos</link><description>After four high school friends are involved in a hit-and-run road accident, they dispose of the body and vow to keep the incident a secret. A year later, they each start receiving anonymous letters bearing the warning "I Know What You Did Last Summer."</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 00:04:18 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>t1g8rsfan</category><guid isPermaLink="false">5e67f331df7bc91ffdd9db5a135841ff7975cee44fc97efdee531a20e9090e65</guid></item><item><title>I Still Know What You Did Last Summer</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/t1g8rsfan/i-still-know-what-you-did-last-summer/#atmos</link><description>Ever since killing the Fisherman one year ago, Julie James is still haunted by images of him after her. When her best friend Karla wins free tickets to the Bahamas, Julie finds this a perfect opportunity to finally relax. But someone is waiting for her. Someone who she thought was dead. Someone who is out again for revenge.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 00:04:18 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>t1g8rsfan</category><guid isPermaLink="false">f84a4ab153dda88eeadbafdf71d33a497c383e10dde7a18238bffd5cc403054f</guid></item><item><title>Scream 2</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/t1g8rsfan/scream-2/#dts-hd-ma-51</link><description>Away at college, Sidney thought she'd finally put the shocking murders that shattered her life behind her... until a copycat killer begins acting out a real-life sequel.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 00:04:18 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>t1g8rsfan</category><guid isPermaLink="false">b4ab06064a563d98fa178700cc7fed55a7532b106fed97bc4ca9abf741703c76</guid></item><item><title>Scream 3</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/t1g8rsfan/scream-3/#dts-hd-ma-51</link><description>While Sidney lives in safely guarded seclusion, bodies begin dropping around the Hollywood set of STAB 3, the latest movie based on the gruesome Woodsboro killings.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 00:04:18 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>t1g8rsfan</category><guid isPermaLink="false">7b546f3258c3db01725ee02636efe8b892a7b7c82daf65b1e78b2acdfa55d262</guid></item><item><title>Scream 4</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/t1g8rsfan/scream-4/#dts-hd-ma-51</link><description>Sidney returns home to Woodsboro on the last stop of her book tour, which brings about the return of Ghost Face and puts her family, friends, and the whole town in danger.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 00:04:18 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>t1g8rsfan</category><guid isPermaLink="false">fccf370cbd3fa82f4cac4df645055698c30bdfb43640d364e5b1bc0021c30db9</guid></item><item><title>The Boogeyman</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/t1g8rsfan/the-boogeyman/#dts-hd-ma-51</link><description>Still reeling from the tragic death of their mother, a teenage girl and her younger sister find themselves plagued by a sadistic presence in their house and struggle to get their grieving father to pay attention before it’s too late.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 00:04:18 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>t1g8rsfan</category><guid isPermaLink="false">19faa4a4b49e72d9303e54cacfb46c10505319877dbc7afbe12273ff05cce0e3</guid></item><item><title>The Mist</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/t1g8rsfan/the-mist/#atmos</link><description>After a violent storm, a dense cloud of mist envelops a small Maine town, trapping artist David Drayton and his five-year-old son in a local grocery store with other people. They soon discover that the mist conceals deadly horrors that threaten their lives, and worse, their sanity.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 00:04:18 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>t1g8rsfan</category><guid isPermaLink="false">fabe01346c5020dcf65231549df687e31def29d5bc392bbfd0bef2c5316d1180</guid></item><item><title>Wedding Crashers</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/t1g8rsfan/wedding-crashers/#truehd-51</link><description>John and his buddy, Jeremy are emotional criminals who know how to use a woman's hopes and dreams for their own carnal gain. Their modus operandi: crashing weddings. Normally, they meet guests who want to toast the romantic day with a random hook-up. But when John meets Claire, he discovers what true love – and heartache – feels like.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 00:04:18 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>t1g8rsfan</category><guid isPermaLink="false">059ab89121794fa51d06afaa14ed8c7398ada8ca08513c551a184dcfee00724c</guid></item><item><title>The Bell Keeper</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/the-bell-keeper/#dd-51</link><description>A group of friends travel to a secluded campsite to film a documentary. What they find is something much more sinister than they could have ever imagined.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 18:40:44 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">aeaa3008b4f67fc005df27180e810d795a8c5131b5c586b9b99171b7a783254f</guid></item><item><title>The Lion King</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/the-lion-king/#dts-hd-ma-71-atmos-dd-atmos</link><description>Simba idolizes his father, King Mufasa, and takes to heart his own royal destiny. But not everyone in the kingdom celebrates the new cub's arrival. Scar, Mufasa's brother—and former heir to the throne—has plans of his own. The battle for Pride Rock is ravaged with betrayal, tragedy and drama, ultimately resulting in Simba's exile. With help from a curious pair of newfound friends, Simba will have to figure out how to grow up and take back what is rightfully his.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 18:40:44 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">8ab013b161c64e72a1373c6bea4c6bb4660b3afceb1712fec5a244e0241b33ff</guid></item><item><title>The Princess and the Frog</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/the-princess-and-the-frog/#dd-atmos</link><description>A waitress, desperate to fulfill her dreams as a restaurant owner, is set on a journey to turn a frog prince back into a human being, but she has to face the same problem after she kisses him.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 18:40:44 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">e9e4a5edf81ec5c688cfd960516f03da2a68b4b4947702348fa532aeadb484b7</guid></item><item><title>The Mist</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/halcyon888/the-mist/#atmos</link><description>After a violent storm, a dense cloud of mist envelops a small Maine town, trapping artist David Drayton and his five-year-old son in a local grocery store with other people. They soon discover that the mist conceals deadly horrors that threaten their lives, and worse, their sanity.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 17:20:40 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>halcyon888</category><guid isPermaLink="false">7d418bde4374820eb028aa357b624605f282ad65aae7d7479a4f3d209514f9ff</guid></item><item><title>Chip 'n Dale: Rescue Rangers</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/chip-n-dale-rescue-rangers/#dd-atmos</link><description>Decades since their successful television series was canceled, Chip has succumbed to a life of suburban domesticity as an insurance salesman. Dale, meanwhile, has had CGI surgery and works the nostalgia convention circuit, desperate to relive his glory days. When a former cast mate mysteriously disappears, Chip and Dale must repair their broken friendship and take on their Rescue Rangers detective personas once again to save their friend’s life.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 10:50:57 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">f5b9e66f4a55a533a56a1af923449cf3512a6b96401d3d24d9beb366fca51b80</guid></item><item><title>Christopher Robin</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/christopher-robin/#dd-atmos</link><description>Christopher Robin, the boy who had countless adventures in the Hundred Acre Wood, has grown up and lost his way. Now it’s up to his spirited and loveable stuffed animals, Winnie The Pooh, Tigger, Piglet, and the rest of the gang, to rekindle their friendship and remind him of endless days of childlike wonder and make-believe, when doing nothing was the very best something.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 10:50:57 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">5e108e08cfb0bc25cdb0f3a0c0952941544ac78d4ce09dfd47bb6c17c8f8ea0d</guid></item><item><title>Free Guy</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/free-guy/#atmos-dd-atmos-dts-hd-ma-71</link><description>A bank teller called Guy realizes he is a background character in an open world video game called Free City that will soon go offline.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 10:50:57 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">79417f0ca84fc648c2a587d11002fae0b6a33a1d5e5f07fc396564868d2f2b3b</guid></item><item><title>The Hunt</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/the-hunt_514847/#dts-hd-ma-71-dd-51</link><description>Twelve strangers wake up in a clearing. They don't know where they are—or how they got there. In the shadow of a dark internet conspiracy theory, ruthless elitists gather at a remote location to hunt humans for sport. But their master plan is about to be derailed when one of the hunted turns the tables on her pursuers.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 10:50:57 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">9683c2644459b46a319a31041e046859642c26f9cee8b985a4a2335e3d50442f</guid></item><item><title>The Ice Age Adventures of Buck Wild</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/the-ice-age-adventures-of-buck-wild/#dd-atmos</link><description>The fearless one-eyed weasel Buck teams up with mischievous possum brothers Crash &amp; Eddie as they head off on a new adventure into Buck's home: The Dinosaur World.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 10:50:57 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">e555d5bb0c17db3f3e02bc34f8854216a4fb2c161ea094427dc62801fc4686e2</guid></item><item><title>Ron's Gone Wrong</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/rons-gone-wrong/#atmos-dd-atmos</link><description>In a world where walking, talking, digitally connected bots have become children's best friends, an 11-year-old finds that his robot buddy doesn't quite work the same as the others do.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 10:50:57 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">ba7ddeb82182429b96600f9f39074cfb79eba79b53a35f9f920ed780bee856ba</guid></item><item><title>Secret Society of Second Born Royals</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/secret-society-of-second-born-royals/#dd-atmos</link><description>Sam is a teenage royal rebel, second in line to the throne of the kingdom of Illyria. Just as her disinterest in the royal way of life is at an all-time high, she discovers she has super-human abilities and is invited to join a secret society of similar extraordinary second-born royals charged with keeping the world safe.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 10:50:57 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">10f9d6f0c6b31a48bef94d9aef02c814c70bcea10edba4cdc2b688912d193e54</guid></item><item><title>White Men Can't Jump</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/white-men-cant-jump/#dd-atmos</link><description>Seemingly opposite street hoopers, Jeremy, an injury prone former star, and Kamal, a has-been prodigy, team up to take one final shot at living out their dreams.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 10:50:57 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">8f10e1bda291c88843e54a88098c999a7555353ee0a5723dc43c41a102b95fe4</guid></item><item><title>Pantheon</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/pantheon/#season-1</link><description>A bullied teen receives mysterious help from someone online: a stranger soon revealed to be her recently deceased father, David, whose consciousness has been uploaded to the Cloud following an experimental destructive brain scan. David is the first of a new kind of being – an “Uploaded Intelligence” or “UI” – but he will not be the last, as a global conspiracy unfolds that threatens to trigger a new kind of world war.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 07:42:55 -0000</pubDate><category>TV</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">df786d7c925f1fb3122fb0517c614935fb06b69569f55e12d676bec379edf2ce</guid></item><item><title>Pantheon</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/pantheon/#season-2</link><description>A bullied teen receives mysterious help from someone online: a stranger soon revealed to be her recently deceased father, David, whose consciousness has been uploaded to the Cloud following an experimental destructive brain scan. David is the first of a new kind of being – an “Uploaded Intelligence” or “UI” – but he will not be the last, as a global conspiracy unfolds that threatens to trigger a new kind of world war.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 07:42:55 -0000</pubDate><category>TV</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">5ef602500092cd6b4c5bbc6819614c5bbee228923fb1e6dd060ce3a3c0f26da8</guid></item><item><title>The Power</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/the-power/#dd-51</link><description>It is a hair-raising journey into the world of two lovers as both their families are ripped apart for the sake of revenge and power, and an entertaining look at how they rise out of that pit of blood lust and despair, together.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 03:56:32 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">40717524051b43714123d699b1614431668cafa8f62282130d42edf0ac51b0b6</guid></item><item><title>John Carpenter's Suburban Screams</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/john-carpenters-suburban-screams/#season-1</link><description>Each episode of this horror anthology delves into the monstrous evil that lurks beneath the surface of friendly suburbia through the lens of one frightful tale. In addition to firsthand accounts, the episodes include cinematic reenactments, personal archives, and historic town press coverage.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 00:46:32 -0000</pubDate><category>TV</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">0b2fe54c968e95c8821d18d05d1babad2fb0474c15684bb969f6ea9cba151c3b</guid></item><item><title>Barbie</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/barbie/#atmos</link><description>Barbie and Ken are having the time of their lives in the colorful and seemingly perfect world of Barbie Land. However, when they get a chance to go to the real world, they soon discover the joys and perils of living among humans.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 22:01:41 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">307be9ffce197693249167b0ddc6ecb1479df35dc66e9f88a0c41f4bb22239b1</guid></item><item><title>The 'Burbs</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/t1g8rsfan/the-burbs/#flac-20</link><description>When secretive new neighbors move in next door, suburbanite Ray Peterson and his friends let their paranoia get the best of them as they start to suspect the newcomers of evildoings and commence an investigation. But it's hardly how Ray, who much prefers drinking beer, reading his newspaper and watching a ball game on the tube expected to spend his vacation.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 20:32:28 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>t1g8rsfan</category><guid isPermaLink="false">addb7139700758d084439ee52be7c224160b75a97286be50cba3b0ea81698211</guid></item><item><title>Dangerous Game: The Legacy Murders</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/dangerous-game-the-legacy-murders/#dd-51</link><description>A family reunion at a remote mansion takes a lethal turn when they are trapped inside and forced to play a deadly survival game where only one will make it out alive.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 18:41:22 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">cdb0c00efe3c525b25887c15f5e2cb240d1b5342058de5bb6a2dc3bc8c105258</guid></item><item><title>Disquiet</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/disquiet/#dd-51</link><description>After a near-fatal car accident, Sam wakes to discover he is trapped in an abandoned hospital by mysterious and sinister forces that have no intention of letting him leave…</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 18:41:22 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">b7c440ccd5c04f062ef65b3bed892072cda25470a66294118c32f814c6734c7a</guid></item><item><title>Greyhound</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/greyhound/#dd-atmos</link><description>A first-time captain leads a convoy of allied ships carrying thousands of soldiers across the treacherous waters of the “Black Pit” to the front lines of WW2. With no air cover protection for 5 days, the captain and his convoy must battle the surrounding enemy Nazi U-boats in order to give the allies a chance to win the war.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 18:41:22 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">537417214bae8751a8541edaf900937062e908e709227e500cdc1873aef10901</guid></item><item><title>Invasion</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/halcyon888/invasion/#season-2-episodes-5-6-8</link><description>Earth is visited by an alien species that threatens humanity’s existence. Events unfold in real time through the eyes of five ordinary people across the globe as they struggle to make sense of the chaos unraveling around them.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 15:23:43 -0000</pubDate><category>TV</category><category>halcyon888</category><guid isPermaLink="false">5d433f8f8d2486a571de459709f78fdd5c90e689ffb6b529f18132f3533fdee6</guid></item><item><title>Kingsman: The Secret Service</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/halcyon888/kingsman-the-secret-service/#dts-hd-ma-71</link><description>The story of a super-secret spy organization that recruits an unrefined but promising street kid into the agency's ultra-competitive training program just as a global threat emerges from a twisted tech genius.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 12:28:36 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>halcyon888</category><guid isPermaLink="false">c53a8462fb73020a392c8ebb5a6d064b947f3493609b37a87cec6a77971d8e50</guid></item><item><title>Detective Byomkesh Bakshy!</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/detective-byomkesh-bakshy/#dd-51</link><description>Byomkesh, fresh out of college, agrees to investigate the disappearance of Bhuvan, a chemist. Assisted by Bhuvan's son Ajit, Byomkesh links the case to a larger conspiracy that will unsettle Calcutta.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 10:06:23 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">4e330c490f2de3ed55ad255089b27f962716acab2ad69203f9bf078356f89ad8</guid></item><item><title>Dev.D</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/devd/#dd-51</link><description>Because they come from different castes, the son of a tax collector and his true love are not allowed to marry, sending them down divergent paths.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 10:06:23 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">9dfa32bc3d4eeb0376453bd63f6c803d283504d6ab8836a64ac98b6d0f5b48bf</guid></item><item><title>Dum Laga Ke Haisha</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/dum-laga-ke-haisha/#dd-51</link><description>A slim uneducated guy is pressured into an arranged marriage with an overweight college girl. The mismatched couple is challenged to compete in the annual wife-carrying race.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 10:06:23 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">a767e67a4d1e1688f2e34196bb4fc87d3d2b024727411f9acfa42f66d5412bfa</guid></item><item><title>Fitoor</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/fitoor/#dd-51</link><description>A young artist tries to win the heart of his muse, while her mother hatches a scheme to end his quest for true love.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 10:06:23 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">6725491526891845d6f3f0d0bf5ea6c1e7bb44d0bc8e4c3dfd147d8b3df21de1</guid></item><item><title>Lightyear</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/lightyear/#atmos-dd-atmos-dts-hd-ma-71</link><description>Legendary Space Ranger Buzz Lightyear embarks on an intergalactic adventure alongside a group of ambitious recruits and his robot companion Sox.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 10:06:23 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">d626cc060849bada768b672a01b4c7c0e5717112963e2714da38bd4f0e404935</guid></item><item><title>Shanghai</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/shanghai/#dd-51</link><description>An American man returns to a corrupt, Japanese-occupied Shanghai four months before Pearl Harbor and discovers his friend has been killed. While he unravels the mysteries of the death, he falls in love and discovers a much larger secret that his own government is hiding.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 10:06:23 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">a41344fb56adf77ee1efca0501944c765d832fed0ca179e14618b2804407b431</guid></item><item><title>Blade Runner: Black Lotus</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/blade-runner-black-lotus/#season-1</link><description>Los Angeles 2032. A young woman wakes up with no memories, and possessing deadly skills. The only clues to her mystery are a locked data device and a tattoo of a black lotus. Putting together the pieces, she must hunt down the people responsible for her brutal and bloody past to find the truth of her lost identity.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 10:06:23 -0000</pubDate><category>TV</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">739fd8944be9dc41afcc6a73b472ff2131c22761864e89f55995de910c271d7a</guid></item><item><title>TRON: Uprising</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/tron-uprising/#season-0</link><description>Taking place some time between 'Tron' and 'Tron: Legacy', 'Tron: Uprising' tells the story of Beck, a young program who becomes the skillful leader of a revolution inside the computer world of The Grid.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 10:06:23 -0000</pubDate><category>TV</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">a21812547877df069f66bd5fc2de60455f07b6838ae40a438639ab3a819c823d</guid></item><item><title>TRON: Uprising</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/tron-uprising/#season-1</link><description>Taking place some time between 'Tron' and 'Tron: Legacy', 'Tron: Uprising' tells the story of Beck, a young program who becomes the skillful leader of a revolution inside the computer world of The Grid.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 10:06:23 -0000</pubDate><category>TV</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">c062e4f6e7b140ec44fa77a7ff019248bdd3f22b2f811ac038525203dd9c8be7</guid></item><item><title>Don</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/don/#dts-hd-ma-51</link><description>DCP DeSilva sees a way to bring to justice the feared head of a criminal empire by recruiting a man named Vijay, who looks exactly like the crime boss. The ruse works too well, and soon Vijay finds his life in danger when DeSilva, the only one who knows his true identity, dies.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 03:34:05 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">284d7f953df0dba960a196fd67746b075eadde773d0966c7350c4e0ec0f4f535</guid></item><item><title>Battleship</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/battleship/#dts-hd-ma-51</link><description>When mankind beams a radio signal into space, a reply comes from ‘Planet G’, in the form of several alien crafts that splash down in the waters off Hawaii. Lieutenant Alex Hopper is a weapons officer assigned to the USS John Paul Jones, part of an international naval coalition which becomes the world's last hope for survival as they engage the hostile alien force of unimaginable strength. While taking on the invaders, Hopper must also try to live up to the potential that his brother, and his fiancée's father—an Admiral—expect of him.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 02:44:56 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">cafe5620fcd3b63cf5245bbb00e5b89e2c96b75ef121ecbe9335fa0065cbba6e</guid></item><item><title>The Wedding Guest</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/the-wedding-guest/#dts-hd-ma-51</link><description>Jay is a man with a secret who travels from Britain to Pakistan to attend a wedding—armed with duct tape, a shotgun, and a plan to kidnap the bride-to-be. Jay and his hostage end up on the run across the border and through the railway stations, back alleys, and black markets of New Delhi.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 02:44:56 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">552363d7899eb0ac18705f2f0411500fd699632b918bdc90cf3137b143129e90</guid></item><item><title>Under the Banner of Heaven</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/under-the-banner-of-heaven/#season-1</link><description>A devout detective's faith is tested as he investigates a brutal murder that seems to be connected to an esteemed Utah family's spiral into LDS fundamentalism and their distrust in the government.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 02:44:56 -0000</pubDate><category>TV</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">64fe5a08628a07e4a771ce75b5d665e46de7fe22e827be88079fcfe243b09b4d</guid></item><item><title>Expend4bles</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/t1g8rsfan/expend4bles/#dd-atmos</link><description>Armed with every weapon they can get their hands on and the skills to use them, The Expendables are the world’s last line of defense and the team that gets called when all other options are off the table. But new team members with new styles and tactics are going to give “new blood” a whole new meaning.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2023 23:10:19 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>t1g8rsfan</category><guid isPermaLink="false">75e58790dbab4cb4b729de0575ea4404921f6701132de342fa1f2af119fb31d2</guid></item><item><title>Mission: Impossible - Dead Reckoning Part One</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/t1g8rsfan/mission-impossible-dead-reckoning-part-one/#dd-atmos</link><description>Ethan Hunt and his IMF team embark on their most dangerous mission yet: To track down a terrifying new weapon that threatens all of humanity before it falls into the wrong hands. With control of the future and the world's fate at stake and dark forces from Ethan's past closing in, a deadly race around the globe begins. Confronted by a mysterious, all-powerful enemy, Ethan must consider that nothing can matter more than his mission—not even the lives of those he cares about most.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2023 23:10:19 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>t1g8rsfan</category><guid isPermaLink="false">29f50a5fd538fb28cdd144cd350bad629c92b49c88b4947c66f29d91b33a8fc7</guid></item><item><title>7 Khoon Maaf</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/7-khoon-maaf/#dd-51</link><description>Susanna is hungry for love and will go to any extent to find it in its purest form. In her quest for the perfect man, she gets married a number of times as each of her husband's die mysteriously.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2023 19:29:10 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">33a54fef55d560cd2a02609957341496fa193392936ea64d79e1af9c73d8adcd</guid></item><item><title>Fear the Night</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/fear-the-night/#dd-51</link><description>During a bachelorette party in a secluded California farmhouse, masked intruders launch a brutal attack, forcing eight women to fight for survival. Led by Tess, a troubled military veteran, they unite to defend themselves throughout a harrowing night.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2023 19:29:10 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">21ac59ff6adee5a8a912d69abf54a921512ff5d0a4c23488b3adfc0d59e6d324</guid></item><item><title>Fear the Night</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/fear-the-night/#dts-hd-ma-51</link><description>During a bachelorette party in a secluded California farmhouse, masked intruders launch a brutal attack, forcing eight women to fight for survival. Led by Tess, a troubled military veteran, they unite to defend themselves throughout a harrowing night.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2023 19:29:10 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">0949367a6e2fa74ed10c076d093a9a1068beec8707d305cfc0c9227d2c370057</guid></item><item><title>Haseen Dillruba</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/haseen-dillruba/#dd-atmos</link><description>Under investigation as a suspect in her husband's murder, a wife reveals details of their thorny marriage that seem to only further blur the truth.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2023 19:29:10 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">92b7cf19cd29760b01c278c3af17d46548bbc487c34a94ffbc43265518d2b0fc</guid></item><item><title>Midnight's Children</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/midnights-children/#dts-hd-ma-51</link><description>The story of a pair of children born within moments of India gaining independence from England, growing up in the country that is nothing like their parent's generation. A Canadian-British film adaptation of Salman Rushdie's novel of the same name.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2023 19:29:10 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">53dce512ffba22b54b1c80500bbd331ae3973739e0998cf4d91a42707ee71a07</guid></item><item><title>Underwater</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/underwater/#dts-hd-ma-71-dd-atmos-dd-51-dd-51</link><description>After an earthquake destroys their underwater station, six researchers must navigate two miles along the dangerous, unknown depths of the ocean floor to make it to safety in a race against time.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2023 19:29:10 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">483f495bbfb06e7b5540c276f444559c660a75e0710cfe8cf2783f69fe646729</guid></item><item><title>Vadh</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/vadh/#dd-51</link><description>Shambhunath Mishra, a retired middle school teacher is living a mundane middle-class life with his wife Manju Mishra in Gwalior. Life takes a complete turn for the Mishra family when a situation gets out of hand and it leads to a killing at the hands of Shambhunath Mishra. Mishra ji has very little time to plan cautiously to turn this into a “perfect murder” and leave no trace behind.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2023 19:29:10 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">89c465ab739110ca1bb2481d51cfe430db050e2cb6cf6f677d3df20e9ebc65f2</guid></item><item><title>Expend4bles</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/expend4bles/#dd-atmos-dd-51</link><description>Armed with every weapon they can get their hands on and the skills to use them, The Expendables are the world’s last line of defense and the team that gets called when all other options are off the table. But new team members with new styles and tactics are going to give “new blood” a whole new meaning.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2023 18:46:47 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">8befcb86a4d258eb1556299457872df4e6d8f21d3f594faea09b53d8d02f6c48</guid></item><item><title>Gen V</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/halcyon888/gen-v/#season-1-episodes-1-5</link><description>At America's only college for superheroes, gifted students put their moral boundaries to the test, competing for the university's top ranking, and a chance to join The Seven, Vought International's elite superhero team. When the school's dark secrets come to light, they must decide what kind of heroes they want to become.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2023 15:53:15 -0000</pubDate><category>TV</category><category>halcyon888</category><guid isPermaLink="false">23d94c50e7c67ecd29984f927deb1df90ee2ed2c212d2ed0d98c6e5929a48a1e</guid></item><item><title>Loki</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/halcyon888/loki/#season-2-episode-2</link><description>After stealing the Tesseract during the events of “Avengers: Endgame,” an alternate version of Loki is brought to the mysterious Time Variance Authority, a bureaucratic organization that exists outside of time and space and monitors the timeline. They give Loki a choice: face being erased from existence due to being a “time variant” or help fix the timeline and stop a greater threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2023 15:53:15 -0000</pubDate><category>TV</category><category>halcyon888</category><guid isPermaLink="false">1336017d6d17efade7d6f82720737789bd09159a54bf0e9ad30a386480135896</guid></item><item><title>The Conference</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/the-conference/#dd-atmos</link><description>A team-building conference for municipal employees which turns into a nightmare when accusations of corruption begin to circulate and plague the work environment. At the same time, a mysterious figure begins murdering the participants.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2023 07:52:21 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">81435fbf15aa7712abd17faecdfa01bdbd90442b157aa44d5e1a3762f958a2c3</guid></item><item><title>Awareness</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/awareness/#dd-51</link><description>Ian is a teenager who lives with his father on the outskirts by running small scams using Ian's ability to generate visual illusions upon unsuspecting victims. When one of his cons goes awry, his abilities publicly spiral out of control and Ian becomes the target of two rival organizations, each seeking to exploit his powers.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2023 07:04:04 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">6ca6910e6a8331e4c4b113718b1275e5c518f6c3441d4612c7564434c3cca9ef</guid></item><item><title>Kasargold</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/kasargold/#dd-51</link><description>A young, unassuming gold smuggler and his companion embark on an outrageously risky plan with the hope of gaining a fortune that could secure them a lifetime of wealth.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2023 07:04:04 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">c24131717696e373ad94751029542ba92c6b4b5fef70a68a2eed203bfc06a5d5</guid></item><item><title>Mark Antony</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/mark-antony/#dd-51</link><description>Set in 1995, Mark, a skilled mechanic and the son of a former gangster, stumbles upon a phone that has the ability to connect with the past, tries to save his estranged mother from a grim fate. While facing his own family's legacy, Mark must navigate through dangerous consequences of altering the past, as it causes unforeseen repercussions in the present.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2023 07:04:04 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">fde58819f377adf43246b81fd4dbf54086ba797cf78c0c442b9de084b5277b64</guid></item><item><title>Dark Harvest</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/dark-harvest/#dd-51</link><description>In a cursed town, the annual harvest becomes a brutal battle for survival. On Halloween 1963, Sawtooth Jack, a terrifying legend, rises from the cornfields, threatening the town’s children. Groups of boys unite to defeat the murderous scarecrow before midnight. Richie, a rebellious outcast, joins the run, motivated by his brother’s previous victory. As the hunt progresses, Richie makes a shocking discovery and faces a pivotal choice to break the relentless cycle.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2023 05:27:06 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">6f0b56b519d4cb6400e3193c5104d56a770956ca43b1f0f5367b33ed0fdd71ec</guid></item><item><title>The Burial</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/the-burial/#dd-atmos-dd-51</link><description>A lawyer helps a funeral home owner save his family business from a corporate behemoth. In a move to bring resonance to a dry case, the lawyer digs up a complex web of race, power, and oppression that forces everyone to examine prejudices.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2023 05:19:50 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">f55acdeb3b2366fe18b1bcf7a501f8838dbcc7950e3587f7f431fabf1624dd0f</guid></item><item><title>Goliyon Ki Raasleela Ram-Leela</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/goliyon-ki-raasleela-ram-leela/#dts-hd-ma-71</link><description>Ran and Leela are passionately in love with each other. The only problem is that their respective clans have been enemies for 500 years.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2023 00:09:18 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">3dcc3c70f9af953b68c895b42910d91db29e4706cc0189183cb237275f576d0f</guid></item><item><title>Fantasy Island</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/fantasy-island/#dts-hd-ma-51-dd-51</link><description>A group of contest winners arrive at an island hotel to live out their dreams, only to find themselves trapped in nightmare scenarios.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2023 22:52:51 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">f4cd015c843dc22af6f1c01ca726f5faa62305523a93f6d6e8d90d20bded9fe0</guid></item><item><title>Johnny Gaddaar</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/johnny-gaddaar/#dd-51</link><description>Vikram decides to elope with his girlfriend Mini for a better life. For this purpose he decides to steal the money collected by his business partners for a drug deal. Everything goes horribly wrong when the partner carrying the money, Shiva, is accidentally killed.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2023 22:52:51 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">cf6900548f16e9072e72f5715afad3c496253c29b75ab41784cc43eb1d860611</guid></item><item><title>Gentleman</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/gentleman/#dts-hd-ma-51</link><description>A stylish crime, action film about a CEO of a private detective agency and a prosecutor to catch the axis of evil.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2023 21:41:25 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">cb242bc1a8ab8b29f81f0f66af6734e8120a40940c37d8cb1192f0fac3a8b404</guid></item><item><title>Madras Cafe</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/madras-cafe/#truehd-71</link><description>An Indian intelligence agent journeys to a war-torn coastal island to break a resolute rebel group and meets a passionate journalist.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2023 21:41:25 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">9c5778aac536acbab9049139153d7322d00294b09d5fca2a73acb8413347a3c2</guid></item><item><title>Raees</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/raees/#dts-hd-ma-51</link><description>Set in the early ’80s and ’90s in Gujarat, India, ‘Raees’ is a fictitious story of a crime lord named Raees, who builds an entire empire from scratch, and a police officer who is determined to bring him down.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2023 21:41:25 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">adb4e1eaf854cfb5e7bb1d7c2afce3ab4d6579804e5d28056dff08528a9fa674</guid></item><item><title>Don 2</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/don-2/#dts-hd-ma-51-dd-51</link><description>Having conquered the Asian underworld, crime boss Don sets in motion a plan that will give him dominion over Europe.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2023 11:02:38 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">271fe2705d34c7ed6928d056767512c58936d631debf64b4d2c33f7a9432d2b1</guid></item><item><title>The Fall of the House of Usher</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/the-fall-of-the-house-of-usher/#season-1</link><description>Ruthless siblings Roderick and Madeline Usher have built Fortunato Pharmaceuticals into an empire of wealth, privilege and power. But past secrets come to light when the heirs to the Usher dynasty start dying at the hands of a mysterious woman from their youth.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2023 11:02:38 -0000</pubDate><category>TV</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">103c711f4cebc7df3c8d0042d4097b54bbaacaecbca8617cee9ff7bfb07496b2</guid></item><item><title>Appendage</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/appendage/#dd-51</link><description>After hitting a breaking point, Hannah's inner thoughts physicalize into a monstrous creature that threatens to upend her life.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2023 09:07:34 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">9d825a1eda46b096d20f50ef217a52d978b07f72ae4e78d9bbccfef4c5511ab5</guid></item><item><title>Bullett Raja</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/bullett-raja/#dts-hd-ma-51</link><description>A common man who transforms into a gangster revolts against the very system he once obediently followed by declaring war on the police, the government, and the industrialists.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2023 09:07:34 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">b6f0365fe2344c053c3edc1bb309d960c7c7275a308dbe156bfe19749c8bf953</guid></item><item><title>Jesus Revolution</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/jesus-revolution/#dd-51</link><description>In the 1970s, aimless teenager Greg Laurie searches for all the right things in all the wrong places until he meets Lonnie Frisbee, a charismatic hippie/street preacher. Together with local pastor Chuck Smith, they open the doors of a languishing church to an unexpected revival.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2023 09:07:34 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">e3be08114c130c70680e61e2acea563d9aa714c6a706735e60628cdc21e2a049</guid></item><item><title>Lost Girls &amp; Love Hotels</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/lost-girls-love-hotels/#dd-51</link><description>Searching for escape in Tokyo's back alleys, a haunted English teacher explores love and lust with a dashing Yakuza, as their tumultuous affair takes her on a journey through the city's dive bars and three-hour love hotels.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2023 09:07:34 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">daad93a96714af4fe9563cf7d480905a26c9fe6efef0ba93b2c1d57701fc946d</guid></item><item><title>Neerja</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/neerja/#dts-hd-ma-51</link><description>Neerja is a portrayal on the life of the courageous Neerja Bhanot, who sacrificed her life while protecting the lives of 359 passengers on the Pan Am flight 73 in 1986. The flight was hijacked by a terrorist organization.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2023 09:07:34 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">69101f685d64a548013f1e1ebd424a900b7a880b0c3f8bf760e806254de6b693</guid></item><item><title>Race 2</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/race-2/#dts-hd-ma-51</link><description>Ranveer Singh (Saif Ali Khan) travels to exotic locales and confronts the Turkish mafia on a mission to avenge the death of his lover Sonia in this action-packed sequel. In the process of seeking her killers, Ranveer crosses Armaan Mallick (John Abraham) and Aleena (Deepika Padukone) -- two of the most feared figures in the Turkish underworld. Meanwhile, Ranveer's loyal friend RD (Anil Kapoor) and his new partner Cherry (Amisha Patel) offer a helping hand in a world where love is cheap and trust is a luxury most agents can't afford.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2023 09:07:34 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">994a20ec53217b66eb95fb6f8b4f1a3fcdbd5506e42eda1caccbc91405bc18f2</guid></item><item><title>Savage</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/savage/#dts-hd-ma-51-dd-51</link><description>Buried by treacherous conditions at the top of Mt. Baekdu, a policeman must brave the extreme weather until his transfer comes through. When a group of thieves stumbles into the station in search of safe shelter, both sides must fight for survival.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2023 09:07:34 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">c021b4085ae8955d2c55bcbeb24532281cec7cae12a70782eed6bb87707de2b5</guid></item><item><title>Son of Sardaar</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/son-of-sardaar/#dts-hd-ma-51</link><description>A Punjabi man returning to India falls in love with a woman whose family welcomes him as a guest before realizing he is the man they need to kill in order to avenge their loved ones.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2023 09:07:34 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">53e06d6652c71ad7fb44ec56a45787dcc46debceded79e50f6115b44cc066641</guid></item><item><title>Welcome Back</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/welcome-back/#dts-hd-ma-71</link><description>A pair of reformed gangsters try to find a husband for their newly discovered sister, but complications arise due to mistaken identities.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2023 09:07:34 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">a342762791467d593bfda839d73b0e44374e579f990cf1bc5e6231a9ae341caf</guid></item><item><title>Khuda Haafiz</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/khuda-haafiz/#dd-51</link><description>When the 2008 recession leaves Sameer Chaudhary and his wife Nargis jobless, they struggle to make a living and after three months, succeed when they find jobs in a Middle East country named Noman. Due to delay in arrival of documents, Sameer stays in India while Nargis heads to Noman, upon arriving where she is abducted as she pleads for help over a phone call to Sameer. Enraged and helpless, Sameer heads to Noman and teams up with a local taxi driver to find Nargis before it is too late.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2023 00:17:26 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">f1dfd2d5c6378f7248e565bdc77472823a8189d988c883c8a4ac1e920f84f9d6</guid></item><item><title>Khuda Haafiz Chapter 2: Agni Pariksha</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/khuda-haafiz-chapter-2-agni-pariksha/#dd-51</link><description>Following a traumatic chapter in their lives, Sameer and Nargis try to lead a happy life by adopting Nandini, a friend's orphaned niece. But fate soon strikes back hard when Nandini goes missing.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2023 00:17:26 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">e78e34054a71f9053d154849ac78f47a852305dd3e0c42b58d3bec93b3e14845</guid></item><item><title>Rangoon</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/rangoon/#atmos</link><description>Julia travels to the Indo-Burma border to perform for the troops during the World War II, on the insistence of Billimoria, her lover. She finds herself in love with Jemadar Malik, a soldier there.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2023 09:02:59 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">b7ea78baa3376b6f36f450feb2febb9c0a0b8c8e7e0a480983ea68dd3e1cfebf</guid></item><item><title>Tadap</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/tadap/#dd-51</link><description>Passionate Ishana falls madly in love with Ramisa. As their love grows stronger by the day, fate plays the villain and throws one hurdle after another.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2023 09:02:59 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">d06dcf2e916391c9eb7df21c49bfae0283f5ad959601f415f635f6884b2b9621</guid></item><item><title>Luca</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/luca/#atmos</link><description>Luca and his best friend Alberto experience an unforgettable summer on the Italian Riviera. But all the fun is threatened by a deeply-held secret: they are sea monsters from another world just below the water’s surface.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2023 08:12:21 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">72db1ac39f93f562b493f0c3e31793c4250baf00fe6e3c997219b273f4ee2510</guid></item><item><title>Uri: The Surgical Strike</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/uri-the-surgical-strike/#dts-hd-ma-51</link><description>Following the roguish terrorist attacks at Uri Army Base camp in Kashmir, India takes the fight to the enemy, in its most successful covert operation till date with one and only one objective of avenging their fallen heroes.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2023 08:12:21 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">c781754017c185e027847a2a7b99b446f8a132c4ab7452dc1e7350ed06377c77</guid></item><item><title>Transformers: Rise of the Beasts</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/transformers-rise-of-the-beasts/#dd-atmos</link><description>When a new threat capable of destroying the entire planet emerges, Optimus Prime and the Autobots must team up with a powerful faction known as the Maximals. With the fate of humanity hanging in the balance, humans Noah and Elena will do whatever it takes to help the Transformers as they engage in the ultimate battle to save Earth.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2023 07:13:01 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">e7d7747492883dfab5b25e53c53b8413faa6e806cd1813136c6f778f6e085446</guid></item><item><title>Pet Sematary: Bloodlines</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/pet-sematary-bloodlines/#dd-atmos</link><description>In 1969, a young Jud Crandall has dreams of leaving his hometown of Ludlow, Maine behind, but soon discovers sinister secrets buried within and is forced to confront a dark family history that will forever keep him connected to Ludlow.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 08:21:28 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">15f3d5aef06f1f2b276214b4cbb6de8b57b6a55f4853fc19b61482df874968f5</guid></item><item><title>Spy</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/spy/#dts-hd-ma-71-dd-51</link><description>A desk-bound CIA analyst volunteers to go undercover to infiltrate the world of a deadly arms dealer, and prevent diabolical global disaster.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 00:49:24 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">039aeb6fe677b4f011fb76ff97ef6942e196e3884cb05915ce3459109594ce13</guid></item><item><title>The Banshees of Inisherin</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/the-banshees-of-inisherin/#dd-51</link><description>Two lifelong friends find themselves at an impasse when one abruptly ends their relationship, with alarming consequences for both of them.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2023 19:44:05 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">3375395ebe3d4e02034f957967aeb777382eca9f24e7bedf28bab265bcf5df16</guid></item><item><title>Gadar: Ek Prem Katha</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/gadar-ek-prem-katha/#dd-51</link><description>Amongst the communal riots that erupt in the city, Tara shelters a wayward Sakina from a crazed mob and a bond that blossoms into love is created. The two eventually get married and have a son. The happy family, now living in Amritsar, gets the shock of their lives when Sakina learns that her father (Amrish Puri), whom she previously believed died in the riots back in Amritsar, is still alive after seeing his picture in a tattered, old newspaper. Upon contacting him, Sakina's father, now the mayor of Lahore in Pakistan, arranges for his daughter to arrive in Lahore to see him. Sakina leaves for Lahore minus Tara and her son, and upon reaching the city, learns of her father's plans for her - plans that include forcing Sakina to forget about her family and start life anew in Pakistan. Then begins an extraordinary journey which will lead Tara to cross the border into Pakistan to find his love Sakina</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2023 19:44:05 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">c684c5b7902a506de36fdabec030daefc42bf38eb0c7189f504b8809299af6e2</guid></item><item><title>Mission: Impossible - Dead Reckoning Part One</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/halcyon888/mission-impossible-dead-reckoning-part-one/#dd-atmos</link><description>Ethan Hunt and his IMF team embark on their most dangerous mission yet: To track down a terrifying new weapon that threatens all of humanity before it falls into the wrong hands. With control of the future and the world's fate at stake and dark forces from Ethan's past closing in, a deadly race around the globe begins. Confronted by a mysterious, all-powerful enemy, Ethan must consider that nothing can matter more than his mission—not even the lives of those he cares about most.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2023 19:13:28 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>halcyon888</category><guid isPermaLink="false">0bdd796cc5a1d23e26eb9597d233f8c4187fa2b0e27a74a1df9b7c35021df812</guid></item><item><title>Elemental</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/elemental/#atmos-dd-atmos</link><description>In a city where fire, water, land and air residents live together, a fiery young woman and a go-with-the-flow guy will discover something elemental: how much they have in common.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2023 18:59:37 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">cc008481e45df2bb1ba67587817da5b335ab0917820ad4f5c1ace11fea64b56d</guid></item><item><title>Mission: Impossible - Dead Reckoning Part One</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/mission-impossible-dead-reckoning-part-one/#dd-atmos</link><description>Ethan Hunt and his IMF team embark on their most dangerous mission yet: To track down a terrifying new weapon that threatens all of humanity before it falls into the wrong hands. With control of the future and the world's fate at stake and dark forces from Ethan's past closing in, a deadly race around the globe begins. Confronted by a mysterious, all-powerful enemy, Ethan must consider that nothing can matter more than his mission—not even the lives of those he cares about most.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2023 18:59:37 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">a2b5021a4095b7671266bae25d99e0c8261dcb929ae0d9dc0d90df04a9cd5836</guid></item><item><title>Gadar 2</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/gadar-2/#dd-atmos</link><description>When Tara Singh goes missing during a skirmish and is believed to be captured in Pakistan, his son Jeete sets out to rescue him and enters a labyrinth from which they both must escape at all costs.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2023 09:59:03 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">6aecdfde4f158444e1a6f0912a396356820c5b25e82a91da10dae17d654e56c2</guid></item><item><title>Fukrey</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/fukrey/#dd-51</link><description>The paths of four dream-chasing college friends cross with an array of colourful characters, from a tough-talking Punjabi female don to a Jugaad Baaz college watchman. Mayhem ensues.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2023 09:34:22 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">448ae5e7eac763b2b0671710b5a1b7116b58870837613eeebf1289ebd582b9d3</guid></item><item><title>The Menu</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/the-menu_593643/#dd-atmos-dts-hd-ma-51</link><description>A young couple travels to a remote island to eat at an exclusive restaurant where the chef has prepared a lavish menu, with some shocking surprises.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2023 09:34:22 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">25845de2f5d8f72a8dfd57a667bfb786a787e137f9d1af89180ea001aeff6628</guid></item><item><title>Pad Man</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/pad-man/#dd-51</link><description>Upon realizing the extent to which women are affected by their menses, a man sets out to create a sanitary pad machine and to provide inexpensive sanitary pads to the women of rural India.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2023 09:34:22 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">ca2054805d7cba60fa7feca8396f6b326cf31b10d934f0019472793580e7f835</guid></item><item><title>Toilet: A Love Story</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/toilet-a-love-story/#dd-51</link><description>A woman threatens to leave her husband unless he installs a toilet in their home. To win back her love and respect, he heads out on a journey to fight against the backward society.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2023 09:34:22 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">c71ee5572cdbe3dd4925a7535ca0736d974ad58c5d932303a6b71322a7e6c78a</guid></item><item><title>Elemental</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/t1g8rsfan/elemental/#atmos</link><description>In a city where fire, water, land and air residents live together, a fiery young woman and a go-with-the-flow guy will discover something elemental: how much they have in common.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2023 00:23:21 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>t1g8rsfan</category><guid isPermaLink="false">10e6bac0458aacfa74dd0a3d01089a47898a1f6cd1f84bf743bf9d7cff462ab7</guid></item><item><title>Chandni Chowk to China</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/chandni-chowk-to-china/#dd-51</link><description>Based in Delhi's Chandni Chowk, orphaned Sidhu is adopted by the owner of Bajrang Bali Parathas, known simply as Dada. Years later Sidhu has grown up and is an expert at slicing vegetables.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Oct 2023 09:44:54 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">a025726194a64769b40617b9a789fe60b442f103bab52ccf9dd5d94d14db9d9e</guid></item><item><title>Raazi</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/raazi/#dts-hd-ma-51-dd-51</link><description>An Indian spy is married to a Pakistani military officer during the Indo-Pakistani War of 1971.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Oct 2023 09:44:54 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">941b0507940b6f95037d32465f646402e292419d899557ccf1546572b590badc</guid></item><item><title>Te3n</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/te3n/#dts-hd-ma-51</link><description>A grandfather, police officer and a priest join hands to investigate and find a missing child.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Oct 2023 09:44:54 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">df1503137777fd7931e8eda8b793aa40fac3f6fb7d70b6d9ec2e4d33d143f43b</guid></item><item><title>Death Race</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/death-race/#dts-hd-ma-51</link><description>Terminal Island, New York: 2020. Overcrowding in the US penal system has reached a breaking point. Prisons have been turned over to a monolithic Weyland Corporation, which sees jails full of thugs as an opportunity for televised sport. Adrenalized inmates, a global audience hungry for violence and a spectacular, enclosed arena come together to form the 'Death Race', the biggest, most brutal event.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Oct 2023 03:07:38 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">4e770581d2ff17bc1ef02e1e13b780b57ea89ec5149c888247b8d6964f6df444</guid></item><item><title>Radhe</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/radhe/#dd-51</link><description>As Mumbai’s youth are falling prey to rampant drug abuse, suspended cop Radhe is recalled for a clean-up mission. But Radhe is up against a dangerous new outlaw Rana, who will stop at nothing to rule the city.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Oct 2023 02:37:07 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">ad4b0004a834172831ffb98ce41ccf50c14ab4de77a1f00ef339214849e1e825</guid></item><item><title>Radhe</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/radhe/#dts-ex-51</link><description>As Mumbai’s youth are falling prey to rampant drug abuse, suspended cop Radhe is recalled for a clean-up mission. But Radhe is up against a dangerous new outlaw Rana, who will stop at nothing to rule the city.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Oct 2023 02:37:07 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">236a7932a2d7482d1a6d104027e7e8edc4cbf0e9272966e459905914481c180f</guid></item><item><title>Pumpkinhead</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/pumpkinhead/#dts-hd-ma-51</link><description>After a tragic accident, a man conjures up a towering, vengeful demon called Pumpkinhead to destroy a group of unsuspecting teenagers.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Oct 2023 01:09:12 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">62dcf611b03be94b1b172e28c87789001fd014ad332cf110e97e54e599b649fc</guid></item><item><title>Daybreakers</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/halcyon888/daybreakers/#dd</link><description>In the year 2019, a plague has transformed almost every human into a vampire. Faced with a dwindling blood supply, the fractured dominant race plots their survival; meanwhile, a researcher works with a covert band of vampires on a way to save humankind.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Oct 2023 00:07:11 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>halcyon888</category><guid isPermaLink="false">35f173cec3a1b5dfc760d37c761762a62bd8e0cf0b87b780975a07edbe823c51</guid></item><item><title>Pretty Woman</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/pretty-woman/#dts-hd-ma-51</link><description>When a millionaire wheeler-dealer enters a business contract with a Hollywood hooker Vivian Ward, he loses his heart in the bargain.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Oct 2023 22:14:24 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">ed31200de06bb29a0627d4e5f4a297d7a32e85518124057ead998a94566d6f5d</guid></item><item><title>Ek Villain</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/ek-villain/#dd-51</link><description>An ex-gangster reenters the world of violence after his pregnant wife is murdered and torments the killer by capturing and releasing him again and again.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Oct 2023 19:45:00 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">b1d892c2c43644a8f30df9aa01647f9860f34a9fe76ea56f72c02fa9163967dc</guid></item><item><title>Laxmii</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/laxmii/#dd-51</link><description>Aasif's belief in logic and science shatters when he gets possessed by a transgender's ghost.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Oct 2023 19:45:00 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">cdcf456398c1b464cb37d5c3a7615054674a253bc2a38a7aee36bdf86c6d818b</guid></item><item><title>Mardaani</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/mardaani/#dd-51</link><description>A Mumbai police officer's search for a missing teenage girl leads her to the depraved world of child trafficking. What follows is a cat-and-mouse game between the officer and a ruthless mafia kingpin.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Oct 2023 19:45:00 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">274b6f854b13a5358021f59cf8a58a77e47636db320879224a74a54448552495</guid></item><item><title>Mardaani 2</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/mardaani-2/#dd-51</link><description>Officer Shivani Shivaji Roy is stationed at Kota where she goes against a ferocious serial killer who rapes and murders women.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Oct 2023 19:45:00 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">0bdfe2bbb01392c376dcf0f4f432a51f53391a4e6337a69933ca9a8a1214b996</guid></item><item><title>V/H/S/85</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/vhs85/#dd-51</link><description>Unveiled through a made-for-TV documentary, five chilling tales of found footage horror emerge to take viewers on a gore-filled journey through the grim underbelly of the forgotten 1980s.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Oct 2023 19:45:00 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">5bee6e9d9d13271acee5ffbeef29c2e157d2f59428a10fd67019e77e5d04b758</guid></item><item><title>The Wheel of Time</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/halcyon888/the-wheel-of-time/#season-2-episodes-1-5-7</link><description>Follow Moiraine, a member of the shadowy and influential all-female organization called the “Aes Sedai” as she embarks on a dangerous, world-spanning journey with five young men and women. Moiraine believes one of them might be the reincarnation of an incredibly powerful individual, whom prophecies say will either save humanity or destroy it.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Oct 2023 14:02:13 -0000</pubDate><category>TV</category><category>halcyon888</category><guid isPermaLink="false">851b1d69c0175b463cb4344e96ff7f3fc606d5a7e9e72694d3bd8f82c8318bd8</guid></item><item><title>The Wheel of Time</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/halcyon888/the-wheel-of-time/#season-2-episode-6</link><description>Follow Moiraine, a member of the shadowy and influential all-female organization called the “Aes Sedai” as she embarks on a dangerous, world-spanning journey with five young men and women. Moiraine believes one of them might be the reincarnation of an incredibly powerful individual, whom prophecies say will either save humanity or destroy it.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Oct 2023 14:02:13 -0000</pubDate><category>TV</category><category>halcyon888</category><guid isPermaLink="false">bac05d73c5b3bbeb128825c85071e79f926a5d7a2967203ec4692836ebb398cf</guid></item><item><title>The Wheel of Time</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/halcyon888/the-wheel-of-time/#season-2-episode-8</link><description>Follow Moiraine, a member of the shadowy and influential all-female organization called the “Aes Sedai” as she embarks on a dangerous, world-spanning journey with five young men and women. Moiraine believes one of them might be the reincarnation of an incredibly powerful individual, whom prophecies say will either save humanity or destroy it.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Oct 2023 13:26:54 -0000</pubDate><category>TV</category><category>halcyon888</category><guid isPermaLink="false">008c497abc9416d8bcc0ed02b8caa204a1a3556c7045c3bce6b451bfc5b07beb</guid></item><item><title>The Caine Mutiny Court-Martial</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/the-caine-mutiny-court-martial/#dd-51</link><description>A naval officer stands trial for mutiny after taking command from a ship's captain he felt was acting in an unstable fashion, endangering both the ship and its crew.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Oct 2023 09:35:58 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">9f60f196dafb7022e07fc8b50aeaa87e7fb9564534b0337d31c308ee2a8fd4a2</guid></item><item><title>Desperation Road</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/desperation-road/#dd-51</link><description>After 11 years in a Mississippi state prison, Russell Gaines struggles to leave his past sins behind him as he returns home to his stoic father, Mitchell. One fateful night he meets Maben, a young mother with nothing but a stolen gun and a murdered police deputy to her name. Desperate and on the run, Russell and Maben must trust one another to escape their own circumstances, before the truths of their intertwined violent past threatens to destroy them.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Oct 2023 09:35:58 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">1691e9450794ddb8745a30883a307023641ab627f8ea953d084e1481a5d4fcf0</guid></item><item><title>OMG 2</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/omg-2/#dd-51</link><description>Life is bliss until one day Kanti Sharan Mudgal’s son Vivek is blamed for immoral conduct and expelled from school. Overwhelmed, Kanti plans to leave town until a divine intervention leads him to seek justice by taking those responsible to court.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Oct 2023 09:35:58 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">49a94610caffed34527e60412ba2c23ee6a1e691c8804da59ac5fd2a42d43db4</guid></item><item><title>OMG: Oh My God!</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/omg-oh-my-god/#dd-51</link><description>A shopkeeper takes God to court when his shop is destroyed by an earthquake.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Oct 2023 09:35:58 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">ccbe40f72df6f41621f865c45365dbadef984c676ef8f0b8298cfe322cd70b59</guid></item><item><title>National Treasure: Edge of History</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/national-treasure-edge-of-history/#season-1</link><description>While searching for history's greatest treasure, Jess Valenzuela unburies her family's secret past.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Oct 2023 09:35:58 -0000</pubDate><category>TV</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">20d115240c63e8e4d98f4c21a06e2e5f86b436ca93ce460a0c79539e8737a60e</guid></item><item><title>Student of the Year</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/student-of-the-year/#dd-51</link><description>Several alumni reminisce about their final year at St. Theresa's College and the events that shaped their lives.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2023 23:35:11 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">42bc2d9072083c2d0b5b966ff8e666b173e682dfe8f00ca4a4729ccd199e399b</guid></item><item><title>Student of the Year 2</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/student-of-the-year-2/#dd-51</link><description>A student must overcome bullies and hardships, both academic and romantic, in order to win his college's coveted Student of the Year trophy.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2023 23:35:11 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">75d1eccbd2b6633581ea2b6216226eecf566d086f3483e047bea9ecf86e1a46f</guid></item><item><title>Pearl</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/pearl/#dts-hd-ma-51-dd-atmos</link><description>Trapped on her family’s isolated farm, Pearl must tend to her ailing father under the bitter and overbearing watch of her devout mother. Lusting for a glamorous life like she’s seen in the movies, Pearl’s ambitions, temptations, and repressions collide.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2023 19:45:14 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">43ccca92cdb7b173db88e1af8ece8d4f849f534252c49bd088760f724ad22507</guid></item><item><title>The Continental: From the World of John Wick</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/halcyon888/the-continental-from-the-world-of-john-wick/#season-1-episode-3</link><description>Winston Scott is roped into a world of assassins and must make things right after his brother's attack on the Continental hotel.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2023 18:37:18 -0000</pubDate><category>TV</category><category>halcyon888</category><guid isPermaLink="false">edeca27a06a7338cfc96b9d53288654c0384286ed714af25bd5a39284920240a</guid></item><item><title>The Continental: From the World of John Wick</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/the-continental-from-the-world-of-john-wick/#season-1</link><description>Winston Scott is roped into a world of assassins and must make things right after his brother's attack on the Continental hotel.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2023 18:25:30 -0000</pubDate><category>TV</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">da71fb17c398e0284ed9c7bfc6a7cc5e1aba05a289b339cfbeabe8ff5850ebef</guid></item><item><title>Loki</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/halcyon888/loki/#season-2-episode-1</link><description>After stealing the Tesseract during the events of “Avengers: Endgame,” an alternate version of Loki is brought to the mysterious Time Variance Authority, a bureaucratic organization that exists outside of time and space and monitors the timeline. They give Loki a choice: face being erased from existence due to being a “time variant” or help fix the timeline and stop a greater threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2023 18:02:59 -0000</pubDate><category>TV</category><category>halcyon888</category><guid isPermaLink="false">230d6dbb356548066f17ae8abc88fc718e755af89c78ace9f8161b17ff8b51b6</guid></item><item><title>Gen V</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/halcyon888/gen-v/#season-1-episodes-1-4</link><description>At America's only college for superheroes, gifted students put their moral boundaries to the test, competing for the university's top ranking, and a chance to join The Seven, Vought International's elite superhero team. When the school's dark secrets come to light, they must decide what kind of heroes they want to become.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2023 17:52:15 -0000</pubDate><category>TV</category><category>halcyon888</category><guid isPermaLink="false">c9f34363401144d2fa66777617958a38d0417bf3ff7313feeacba27d82f233a6</guid></item><item><title>Totally Killer</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/t1g8rsfan/totally-killer/#dd-dd-atmos</link><description>When the infamous "Sweet Sixteen Killer" returns 35 years after his first murder spree to claim another victim, 17-year-old Jamie accidentally travels back in time to 1987, determined to stop the killer before he can start.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2023 17:42:57 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>t1g8rsfan</category><guid isPermaLink="false">ecbb8535d95e379af0c7fcca346a6f8ed1f788f0df0a43f987b2d323dce1d7d4</guid></item><item><title>Pet Sematary: Bloodlines</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/t1g8rsfan/pet-sematary-bloodlines/#dd-atmos</link><description>In 1969, a young Jud Crandall has dreams of leaving his hometown of Ludlow, Maine behind, but soon discovers sinister secrets buried within and is forced to confront a dark family history that will forever keep him connected to Ludlow.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2023 14:08:16 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>t1g8rsfan</category><guid isPermaLink="false">2e1ff73af3b1280e9569b3bb19d3e5ebbd5aeb09569a33b47008e2a35bc50b94</guid></item><item><title>Fair Play</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/fair-play/#dd-atmos</link><description>An unexpected promotion at a cutthroat hedge fund pushes a young couple's relationship to the brink, threatening to unravel not only their recent engagement but their lives.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2023 08:17:03 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">b6154d660d618b51d0a51c8da4e7f109e074144bf1a2e84ebe581942e4bb6020</guid></item><item><title>Baaghi 2</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/baaghi-2/#dd-51</link><description>A battle-hardened army officer goes in search of his ex-lover's child who is mysteriously kidnapped. Neha reaches out to the only person who can help her with her plight, Ronnie. He goes deep into the underbelly of Goa, facing off against drug lords, menacing Russian henchmen, and blood thirsty animals. Daring stunts, chase sequences, air strikes, bomb blasts and other large-scale action sequences will be done with a bona-fide, larger than life approach, truly making it a spectacle.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2023 08:09:07 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">b4638725aff45cdf67eef03ddf8326b9e698921a3427b67e5a67adacb11159f4</guid></item><item><title>Ballerina</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/ballerina/#dd-atmos</link><description>Grieving the loss of a best friend she couldn't protect, an ex-bodyguard sets out to fulfill her dear friend's last wish: sweet revenge.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2023 07:42:22 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">2ea5e257ade131106e34d092a6c77298d28a445d016f0c8e70329ec449b582d0</guid></item><item><title>Totally Killer</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/totally-killer/#dd-51</link><description>Thirty-five years after the shocking murder of three teens, the infamous "Sweet Sixteen Killer" returns on Halloween night to claim a fourth victim. Seventeen-year-old Jamie ignores her overprotective mom's warning and comes face-to-face with the masked maniac and, on the run for her life, accidentally time travels back to 1987, the year of the original killings. Forced to navigate the unfamiliar and outrageous culture of the 1980s, Jamie teams up with her teen mom to take down the killer once and for all, before she's stuck in the past forever.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2023 04:12:40 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">b5fde981b5a263246f90e880a36c870432ee5480c9ed454c297545b45cf641f2</guid></item><item><title>Anne Rice's Mayfair Witches</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/anne-rices-mayfair-witches/#season-1</link><description>An intuitive young neurosurgeon discovers that she is the unlikely heir to a family of witches. As she grapples with her newfound powers, she must contend with a sinister presence that has haunted her family for generations.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2023 03:55:39 -0000</pubDate><category>TV</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">a4a0bac4c9f55949110c2e8c0860b7b48aebdbd4ec15800d43f7670207ef714d</guid></item><item><title>The Protector</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/the-protector/#season-3</link><description>The epic adventure of Hakan, a young shopkeeper whose modern world gets turned upside down when he learns he’s connected to a secret, ancient order, tasked with protecting Istanbul.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2023 03:47:07 -0000</pubDate><category>TV</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">fd5c46d418c3eaf0df64c18a1acddca8fb5984b8452345bbadde9e9b560c1702</guid></item><item><title>The Wheel of Time</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/the-wheel-of-time/#season-2</link><description>Follow Moiraine, a member of the shadowy and influential all-female organization called the “Aes Sedai” as she embarks on a dangerous, world-spanning journey with five young men and women. Moiraine believes one of them might be the reincarnation of an incredibly powerful individual, whom prophecies say will either save humanity or destroy it.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2023 03:47:07 -0000</pubDate><category>TV</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">b7214786ea631b3ad7cf076357c0a58cf4121d14751f2e1e5cdd55b1419ba8ae</guid></item><item><title>DreamKatcher</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/dreamkatcher/#dd-51</link><description>Gail is forced to come to terms with Josh, her new stepson, at a remote country home. After stealing an evil talisman from a mysterious neighbor, Josh has sinister dreams of his dead mother, who commands Josh to murder Gail. When Josh's dad returns, he and Gail suspect that their son has been possessed by an ancient, bloodthirsty spirit. Is it too late to save Josh's life — or their own?</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 22:44:43 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">04f7f488fc22e5bc954f8b39c20d4125f00886cf1fe05f5877af82f8a5d92d40</guid></item><item><title>Mumbai Diaries</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/mumbai-diaries/#season-1</link><description>A medical thriller set in the Emergency Room of a government hospital. The series explores the challenges faced by the medical staff at the hospital as well as other first responders across the city of Mumbai in dealing with a crisis of immense magnitude. In this battle to save lives and heal others, the ones doing the fixing are the most broken.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 22:44:43 -0000</pubDate><category>TV</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">5f1484b5ac22a7f07c7567acc650bed5fd912f6b64a7f254970a98b7e34839cd</guid></item><item><title>Mumbai Diaries</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/mumbai-diaries/#season-2</link><description>A medical thriller set in the Emergency Room of a government hospital. The series explores the challenges faced by the medical staff at the hospital as well as other first responders across the city of Mumbai in dealing with a crisis of immense magnitude. In this battle to save lives and heal others, the ones doing the fixing are the most broken.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 22:44:43 -0000</pubDate><category>TV</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">af9e369ca05f2c540026ca3b663cd924eee390fde20ec8ae0f5ee40c77f3e89f</guid></item><item><title>Nekrotronic</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/nekrotronic/#dts-hd-ma-51</link><description>A man discovers that he is part of a secret sect of magical beings who hunt down and destroy demons in the internet.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 19:33:33 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">5269fb671d73bf889d38b9f02458c98b0f71176572d92590e6e3653c34523f5a</guid></item><item><title>Hunt Her, Kill Her</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/hunt-her-kill-her/#dts-hd-ma-51</link><description>A desperate young mother, Karen, takes a job as the night shift janitor at a large furniture factory. She is told that she is the only one working at this time. But, after seeing a strange vehicle idling in the parking lot and finding a door to the factory ajar, she gets the feeling she might not be alone after all.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 19:22:33 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">026096c659d6f133a7878cdbec7dcb92832af3c3436e67e7c069b906913fbf59</guid></item><item><title>Raven's Hollow</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/ravens-hollow/#dts-hd-ma-51</link><description>West Point cadet Edgar Allan Poe and four other cadets on a training exercise in upstate New York are drawn by a gruesome discovery into a forgotten community where they find a township guarding a frightening secret.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 19:22:33 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">19f3dc51d33e220404022d975cde9c5eadc9b3894c47c34aecd54f994ff1186c</guid></item><item><title>M3gan</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/m3gan/#atmos</link><description>A brilliant toy company roboticist uses artificial intelligence to develop M3GAN, a life-like doll programmed to emotionally bond with her newly orphaned niece. But when the doll's programming works too well, she becomes overprotective of her new friend with terrifying results.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 19:03:55 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">9cb104f0861691aa4138fa8289ac098f34d42aaef56d1b39b9d5e040bf56a650</guid></item><item><title>The Mist</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/the-mist/#atmos</link><description>After a violent storm, a dense cloud of mist envelops a small Maine town, trapping artist David Drayton and his five-year-old son in a local grocery store with other people. They soon discover that the mist conceals deadly horrors that threaten their lives, and worse, their sanity.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 19:03:55 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">6140dd1a0d6ba69519649a8e64e74ad3be15a01201281179a85a2862084c3041</guid></item><item><title>Khufiya</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/khufiya/#dd-atmos</link><description>When a mole in an intelligence unit leads to the murder of an undercover spy, a hardened agent relentlessly pursues him to avenge the death.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 18:40:46 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">be2f3eec83f813ea95ddc895864e11bf3d9fba759def42362177c75e0723ff26</guid></item><item><title>Lupin</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/lupin/#season-2</link><description>Inspired by the adventures of Arsène Lupin, gentleman thief Assane Diop sets out to avenge his father for an injustice inflicted by a wealthy family.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 18:40:46 -0000</pubDate><category>TV</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">77747f418da9f877fad3821415ee092ca476e55aeeb41209adbcc8aeca6b47e5</guid></item><item><title>Our Flag Means Death</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/our-flag-means-death/#season-1</link><description>After trading in the seemingly charmed life of a gentleman for one of a swashbuckling buccaneer, Stede Bonnet becomes captain of the pirate ship Revenge. Struggling to earn the respect of his potentially mutinous crew, Stede’s fortunes change after a fateful run-in with the infamous Captain Blackbeard. Stede and crew attempt to get their ship together and survive life on the high seas.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 18:40:46 -0000</pubDate><category>TV</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">e1c45996ae98642284916f977381d0beca7d2d7c332c7d93e7204cb16f9794df</guid></item><item><title>The Pale Blue Eye</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/halcyon888/the-pale-blue-eye/#dd-atmos</link><description>West Point, New York, 1830. When a cadet at the burgeoning military academy is found hanged with his heart cut out, the top brass summons former New York City constable Augustus Landor to investigate. While attempting to solve this grisly mystery, the reluctant detective engages the help of one of the cadets: a strange but brilliant young fellow by the name of Edgar Allan Poe</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 17:13:00 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>halcyon888</category><guid isPermaLink="false">baa8a33aa0ba315fd00dbc19a9f34998e7b20b25183f2decd3637bc89e69a9d6</guid></item><item><title>Invasion</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/halcyon888/invasion/#season-2-episode-7</link><description>Earth is visited by an alien species that threatens humanity’s existence. Events unfold in real time through the eyes of five ordinary people across the globe as they struggle to make sense of the chaos unraveling around them.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 16:52:31 -0000</pubDate><category>TV</category><category>halcyon888</category><guid isPermaLink="false">0cd61aaec80285f0d34bfbdf75fe241f19a3647a7c9fb6894ab308cace96a430</guid></item><item><title>Baaghi 3</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/baaghi-3/#dts-hd-ma-51</link><description>A man embarks on a bloody rampage to save his kidnapped brother.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 10:29:57 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">a765c2a6358993609a9a6c6cee13acf3806025b82438b2536983f54e9b4278a3</guid></item><item><title>Gunday</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/gunday/#dd-51</link><description>The lives of Calcutta's most powerful gangsters - Bikram and Bala, changes when Nandita enters it. Then a counter-force takes charge and a thriller unfolds.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 10:29:57 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">7d6a42319e6d968539858810c2d353eb1c15c2d009dbff8af6f6f5a6131b51d9</guid></item><item><title>Jayeshbhai Jordaar</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/jayeshbhai-jordaar/#dd-51</link><description>A non-confrontational Jayesh decides to defy his patriarchal family and flee with his pregnant wife Mudra to save their unborn daughter from foeticide. A screwball, hilarious chase begins as Jayesh's father assembles all his might to nab them. Will this unlikely hero manage to create a safe and equal haven for his daughter?</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 10:29:57 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">f90df9bf008b16ce542edc782058fca20144e4d7e3234df8b1d9125c5cb810dd</guid></item><item><title>Kill Dil</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/kill-dil/#dd-51_to_mono</link><description>Once upon a time in North India, two killers – Dev and Tutu - roamed free. Abandoned when young and vulnerable, Bhaiyaji gave them shelter and nurtured them to kill! All is normal in their lives until destiny throws free-spirited Disha into the mix. What follows is a game of defiance, deception and love.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 10:29:57 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">c09f62024f56d008522e09b4d70bff756050be8c58eb9a03baf0794ce5b4cb50</guid></item><item><title>Koi Jaane Na</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/koi-jaane-na/#dd-51</link><description>A heartbroken writer struggling with writer`s block goes to a quiet hill station where he finds love again but uncovers a copycat serial killer who has mysteriously come alive and is killing everyone around him.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 10:29:57 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">fba413243408ced863ff8151e5e25a8f36477b3ba3da21f091ca0bd3daee4961</guid></item><item><title>London Confidential</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/london-confidential/#dd-51</link><description>A spy-thriller set amidst a series of brutal killings of Indian agents in London, and how Uma, a RAW officer, must expose a mole within the ranks.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 10:29:57 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">3315f4fc40508607f3d639739bcdc50f7b61b6410d0aad1b1c42a932a229eb74</guid></item><item><title>No Surrender</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/no-surrender/#dts-hd-ma-51-dd-51</link><description>Alexandria, Egypt, 1940. Three young Egyptians come to the aid of a woman being attacked by three British soldiers. One of them is arrested and thrown in jail. When the military surrounds the police station and begins an all-out assault, it's up to one man, Gen. Youssef al-Masri, to defend his prison and protect his people.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 10:29:57 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">1e0b8afc1d1a0171545cb8798efc918d1d6177ba37c22fcb0774ce149e341bfc</guid></item><item><title>Pee-Wee's Big Adventure</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/pee-wees-big-adventure/#dd-51</link><description>The eccentric and childish Pee-wee Herman embarks on a big adventure when his beloved bicycle is stolen. Armed with information from a fortune-teller and a relentless obsession with his prized possession, Pee-wee encounters a host of odd characters and bizarre situations as he treks across the country to recover his bike.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 10:29:57 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">511e6e92c9ea2e8d096f6810aafc066298a5f169a897bdd460a6d865c8ff543a</guid></item><item><title>Start-Up</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/start-up/#dts-hd-ma-51</link><description>Taek-il recklessly leaves home, defying his mother who asks him to go to college. In the unfamiliar neighborhood, he happens to get a job as a delivery man for a Chinese restaurant. And he mingles with new people such as Geo-seok, a chef, and Kyung-ju, a boxer. Meanwhile, Sang-pil, a friend of Taek-il, enters the private loan business to make money. At first, it seems easy to make a big fortune, but soon he finds himself in pain as he faces unexpected things.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 10:29:57 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">dc5aa8f9fb3dca692edc95c73f7dd20bf876b1eadef13e0e6fec946636fdd278</guid></item><item><title>Haunted Mansion</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/t1g8rsfan/haunted-mansion/#dd-atmos</link><description>A woman and her son enlist a motley crew of so-called spiritual experts to help rid their home of supernatural squatters.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 23:45:31 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>t1g8rsfan</category><guid isPermaLink="false">417f4939057de29f7e2d38f99c1ace2360616bd4480808d7110fd43310788ea3</guid></item><item><title>Transformers: Rise of the Beasts</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/t1g8rsfan/transformers-rise-of-the-beasts/#atmos-dd-atmos</link><description>When a new threat capable of destroying the entire planet emerges, Optimus Prime and the Autobots must team up with a powerful faction known as the Maximals. With the fate of humanity hanging in the balance, humans Noah and Elena will do whatever it takes to help the Transformers as they engage in the ultimate battle to save Earth.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 23:45:31 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>t1g8rsfan</category><guid isPermaLink="false">9573c599bcc5fd5aacafe7e5761c6ced6e02d1cec17f6b93cac6a8b814af2227</guid></item><item><title>Muzzle</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/halcyon888/muzzle/#dd</link><description>LAPD K-9 officer Jake Rosser has just witnessed the shocking murder of his dedicated partner by a mysterious assailant. As he investigates the shooter’s identity, he uncovers a vast conspiracy that has a chokehold on the city in this thrilling journey through the tangled streets of Los Angeles and the corrupt bureaucracy of the LAPD.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 18:47:51 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>halcyon888</category><guid isPermaLink="false">3e472d9644c168bb45c434f9767db7dad6c1c10a8cf5c11f3f315d1c4804334d</guid></item><item><title>Ahsoka</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/halcyon888/ahsoka/#season-1-episodes-1-4</link><description>Former Jedi Knight Ahsoka Tano investigates an emerging threat to a vulnerable galaxy.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 17:58:57 -0000</pubDate><category>TV</category><category>halcyon888</category><guid isPermaLink="false">0a4cbd4887b748db74193e9507807dda9342ad304617405ce9b426a4bd606faa</guid></item><item><title>Ahsoka</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/halcyon888/ahsoka/#season-1-episodes-5-7</link><description>Former Jedi Knight Ahsoka Tano investigates an emerging threat to a vulnerable galaxy.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 17:58:57 -0000</pubDate><category>TV</category><category>halcyon888</category><guid isPermaLink="false">b2b4727c041136144f68f91adcbc23d4518591506a96e97bc3f554d2ae01559d</guid></item><item><title>Ahsoka</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/halcyon888/ahsoka/#season-1-episode-6</link><description>Former Jedi Knight Ahsoka Tano investigates an emerging threat to a vulnerable galaxy.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 17:58:57 -0000</pubDate><category>TV</category><category>halcyon888</category><guid isPermaLink="false">a6108e79e22d046ef212da9e5b0714262a093c907a431371e2098c4728181efb</guid></item><item><title>Ahsoka</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/halcyon888/ahsoka/#season-1-episode-8</link><description>Former Jedi Knight Ahsoka Tano investigates an emerging threat to a vulnerable galaxy.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 17:58:57 -0000</pubDate><category>TV</category><category>halcyon888</category><guid isPermaLink="false">907bc23a63e19559ddd77a1a753334dddc199a3a9e02522694caca9b35725fe1</guid></item><item><title>Bombshell</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/bombshell/#dts-hd-ma-51-dd-51</link><description>Bombshell is a revealing look inside the most powerful and controversial media empire of all time; and the explosive story of the women who brought down the infamous man who created it.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 08:40:38 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">920d2d12c60d81e15a3d4c314e35f6f114dc659bacbb2f6bb4a407e363094293</guid></item><item><title>Fargo</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/fargo/#dts-hd-ma-51</link><description>Jerry, a small-town Minnesota car salesman is bursting at the seams with debt... but he's got a plan. He's going to hire two thugs to kidnap his wife in a scheme to collect a hefty ransom from his wealthy father-in-law. It's going to be a snap and nobody's going to get hurt... until people start dying. Enter Police Chief Marge, a coffee-drinking, parka-wearing - and extremely pregnant - investigator who'll stop at nothing to get her man. And if you think her small-time investigative skills will give the crooks a run for their ransom... you betcha!</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 08:40:38 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">bac28b0e34e2fee3d809052eed41a3db91fc892105e37f0af6e9f7b275155746</guid></item><item><title>Krrish</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/krrish/#dd-51</link><description>In Singapore, Krishna is forced by circumstances to use his superpowers and become a masked superhero named Krrish, before getting drawn towards his lost legacy.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 08:40:38 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">551ba45b5b81344fd4f17e6c600d5176af762f26fde2df16038035b070d60ed6</guid></item><item><title>The Legend of Bhagat Singh</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/the-legend-of-bhagat-singh/#dd-51</link><description>Born in British India, Bhagat Singh witnesses numerous atrocities during his childhood and grows up to become one of the most fearless freedom fighters in the country.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 08:40:38 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">88cc9da8d4b8e968eb98585a6768dd1d8fdd21233257fc42a0532d8d77163218</guid></item><item><title>Tommy Boy</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/tommy-boy/#truehd-51</link><description>To save the family business, two ne’er-do-well traveling salesmen hit the road with disastrously funny consequences.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 08:40:38 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">f92f9636f041dc4bac79455b8a46e35969dd0c19b561b1773d587d9141da41f9</guid></item><item><title>Transformers: Rise of the Beasts</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/transformers-rise-of-the-beasts/#atmos</link><description>When a new threat capable of destroying the entire planet emerges, Optimus Prime and the Autobots must team up with a powerful faction known as the Maximals. With the fate of humanity hanging in the balance, humans Noah and Elena will do whatever it takes to help the Transformers as they engage in the ultimate battle to save Earth.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 08:40:38 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">708e230745d1b76113412a67d00eec13572c87001411b5775ee5a75dbf26bbb6</guid></item><item><title>Ahsoka</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/ahsoka/#season-1</link><description>Former Jedi Knight Ahsoka Tano investigates an emerging threat to a vulnerable galaxy.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 08:40:38 -0000</pubDate><category>TV</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">f5fe1640c649e4eb37bebf84e440faace0f4d7c29a08dfc949d0b54762408ffa</guid></item><item><title>The Equalizer 3</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/t1g8rsfan/the-equalizer-3/#dd</link><description>Robert McCall finds himself at home in Southern Italy but he discovers his friends are under the control of local crime bosses. As events turn deadly, McCall knows what he has to do: become his friends' protector by taking on the mafia.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 00:27:47 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>t1g8rsfan</category><guid isPermaLink="false">22f6a7a0645e76fae1a36b502c63d71d912f8f1daff22c768f5177aa6f944e25</guid></item><item><title>The Nun II</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/t1g8rsfan/the-nun-ii/#dd-atmos</link><description>In 1956 France, a priest is violently murdered, and Sister Irene begins to investigate. She once again comes face-to-face with a powerful evil.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 00:27:47 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>t1g8rsfan</category><guid isPermaLink="false">c58096371171263603cfe12e67d7429112d7c7ec253ea209db007f8bbd418d48</guid></item><item><title>Haunted Mansion</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/haunted-mansion/#dd-atmos</link><description>A woman and her son enlist a motley crew of so-called spiritual experts to help rid their home of supernatural squatters.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2023 23:03:10 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">b5ad484e533239ba486a8a834aa094e265bc149d8a9cd3fe0f196b74ff7be94e</guid></item><item><title>The Nun II</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/the-nun-ii/#dd-atmos</link><description>In 1956 France, a priest is violently murdered, and Sister Irene begins to investigate. She once again comes face-to-face with a powerful evil.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2023 23:03:10 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">28ece6e39ccb2572c3474309a09682ed5f5f282abfc3f3b579bc6ad35873a71a</guid></item><item><title>Drishyam</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/drishyam/#dts-hd-ma-51</link><description>A simple, street-smart man tries to protect his family from a tough cop looking for his missing son.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2023 21:21:01 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">9dd355b491681b4ddfcfe99f17c1ad7060adc3e738b07af19b2c427257c7b6a3</guid></item><item><title>Secret Headquarters</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/secret-headquarters/#atmos-dd-atmos</link><description>While hanging out after school, Charlie and his friends discover the headquarters of the world’s most powerful superhero hidden beneath his home. When villains attack, they must team up to defend the headquarters and save the world.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2023 21:21:01 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">64ba3758afacbb0ff42057dd5d8769c010699e135b18129bceccf813a9bb8505</guid></item><item><title>How to Blow Up a Pipeline</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/halcyon888/how-to-blow-up-a-pipeline/#dts-hd-ma-51</link><description>A crew of young environmental activists execute a daring mission to sabotage an oil pipeline.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2023 18:31:10 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>halcyon888</category><guid isPermaLink="false">3dac5c2fbf585a3a5465d2348721e90810d1d2f8dbfff569e1957743bca01e99</guid></item><item><title>The Equalizer 3</title><link>https://beqcatalogue.readthedocs.io/en/latest/mobe1969/the-equalizer-3/#dd-51</link><description>Robert McCall finds himself at home in Southern Italy but he discovers his friends are under the control of local crime bosses. As events turn deadly, McCall knows what he has to do: become his friends' protector by taking on the mafia.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2023 18:14:56 -0000</pubDate><category>film</category><category>mobe1969</category><guid isPermaLink="false">149ddcdd46111b8051950fd4c50293a1bcc60b138469f7a7c8d30ec02746acc9</guid></item></channel></rss>